Huh
Hi guys
No, okay, this is really annoying because you know, especially easy to know better like it's just like even if it is like the first on the panel
I don't know that person wants this photo put out there
And I don't know because he's not using his own photo and so it's like I
Just don't I don't know who these people are so you can't use
Photos of other people is just like I'll just kick you off the show. I mean, it's like I can't have it. It's like
Because I have too many people threatening to say oh you're using my people are using my picture
People are putting like, you know breast cancer scars and people repeating people's
Relatives and it's just it's like not I don't think I want on my channel
So stop doing that, please anyone that comes up on the panel. I have to put I mean
I don't want to like have like a million panel rules is this I should be like just like you know
This should be I should have like three, but I now I have like six as it is
I have to maybe have out of the 10, you know, you know, you're not uh
No strange moaning sounds, you know and uh
You know, do you not change your avatar photo and it has to be your own photo? I mean I say I mean
I'm gonna have to write a book guys. It's gonna be it's gonna be a full day
It's like my rules are longer than you should to us at this point. I mean
It's crazy
Anyway, oh, I don't know. Hang on 15 minutes
Still weak
Kind of it two or six on that those real fives
Yeah, so it's the 19th
There's the 19th. Oh my gosh, so in the 21st months of Saturday
That's why I thought the 19th was tomorrow because
Or that I thought tomorrow yeah, because I'm
It's what the
Easy but you can you please stop doing that though like can you start like just like not do that like just just keep
I know it's like you have your own cute profile photos and stuff
Don't pay other people's photos that because that's just like another part of the dog
I can't have that it's like no it's part of the dogs in your room
So you should have, you should have known that it's like no dog thing that's like just don't put other people's photos up that are your own.
I don't even, I don't even like really want people to be using any kind of like, you know,
I just prefer people's own face.
I got you psyche, but for all do like I got you. I'm gonna give you the respect that you say I heard you
I heard you know saying
But in my defense, he was on stage. He's on stage and that's really him
Oh, it's like you and I can check his ID. I mean, I don't know if everyone's just playing a big game
You see
No, he said find them find them all right
This is like you join the join the discord or like
Yeah, just like post stuff like that in there like or like you know pictures media and you can say go go check out the
Discord there's a photo there. I don't know it's like if there's a really need for like people to see certain photo
But it's like otherwise, it's like I think too much too much too much going on for me to keep track of like every
Person's agenda about it. I know you're not doing anything bad
You didn't mean because he stayed talking shit about me. I just do it because he
Oh me put it up there before any show face. So it's not a big big deal. So I'm talking. Yeah
Because he didn't even cry about it you realize
I I know but it you know, it's like people I just I'm getting more paranoid about like people just orchestrating
I know like I know you're not but it's just like
There is this have a lot of people trying to attack my channel. So I'm
Limitations shit I have to be a little bit more straight now
I'm gonna be I'm be a little more sure I'm trying to stick to my anything else. I put up is gonna be cartoonish
So I'm gonna stick to that like drawings and cartoons like the no love picture
I got here and other avatar picture mentally ill but totally chill
All my middle finger like you're gonna put those like this, you know stuff only me I get you I got you like that
Only like that. No other people. I got you
And this one this are funny
No, I'm on that's from a movie. So
All the other ones I got with Alex and all my other haters. I'm gonna hold them down. Don't put them
Okay
So how's that we're doing tonight? Yeah, so yeah, but unfortunately like, you know, it ruins the vibe of the thing
Yeah, it's like and but there's really like no it's like easy like it's a thing
It's like there was like it just was out of nowhere
It's like the other night someone played like it was who played that video of like
Juice hall running into the wild. I don't know it was like some old video and it's our elder played it
I was like my eyes. Yeah
That was that was the Friday 13th. That was Nick next like that. And then I was like, oh, he's go bombing
He's go bombing and it made a huge deal about it. And then
But yeah, so I mean, that's I'm gonna get your disc on discord fuck
I mean, yeah, it's to the back chat rocker right in the back and everybody can see it. Yeah, but it don't matter
I'm just here. I mean, if you send me a message on this one, you take this listen
What do you listen? All I'm doing is giving advice. I'm never telling you what to do
I always told you this already always do what you want been telling you this from beginning
So I can fuck what everybody says do what you want. I will give you the advice
You can accept it or you decline it is your choice
No, I mean, I'm happy to take advice.
It's just like, you know, like I said, like, you know,
people like to criticize me like on the air, like, maybe
because it's like, they can't get hold of me.
Yeah, I see it all the time.
Yeah, I'd rather just like, if you have something to say
and you have a good advice about it,
and like, you can kindly contact me privately,
and not just like, and like, you know,
people just have said it in such a rude way.
It's like, oh, you know, you're stupid,
you're doing this wrong, you don't know anything, blah, blah.
It's just like, in this thing.
So that's not really constructive,
or it's just like basically bullying, and it's like,
Have I called you stupid yet?
No, no, no.
No, you didn't, but it was just, it's just like, you know,
I don't, I just like, you know, that's why I get kind of like,
maybe like too sensitive to criticism is because it's like,
it's like,
Open criticism is good, but just, it's just a delivery.
If people can work on their delivery system or how to give open criticism,
then it's gonna be more than a vice, do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Oh, it's okay.
It's just, you know, I'm just trying to...
But yeah, you can get earlier today,
or Black Archie was saying, Black Archie was saying,
hey, okay, okay, bye, bye.
Hello.
I don't feel like that right now.
I don't need to hear your 50 times
when I'm trying to make a point.
Okay, so I'm trying to say,
It's like fucking grow up guys. It's like, you know, please
Go guys go do your own show and do that shit guys guys do that
It's they know nobody on the right minds gonna put up with this shit anymore
I mean, it's like it's like it's been too less than two it's too much
It's like I just imagine if someone like did this on like there's a lot of channels
I know like you know if they had open panels and people were came on acting so foolishly
Come here. There's the only panel I've been on lately like for the last month or two months
Yeah, I don't have to go to another panel. So I've just been chilling here. I go to beat up recently
I went to have today. I'm maybe twice
In summers once in a blue Tokyo ish
Probably oh money for 20. That's a definitely but other than that that's the only kind of I go to and that's when you're not live
Yeah, yeah, so they can sit they guys you can talk good guys
Go say you're as many times as you want in the back chat. You can and then you can say to each other
I'm not I probably won't take the back chat unless you know if there's anything important back there
You can just let me know but
Yeah, you see just a year in the back. I personally
Those kind of words make me cringe, but it's cool.
I thought it was Sandman's word and then last night I found this streamer.
He's like a really
He's a really small streamer and the first streaming. I was called your it's a
It was made like six months ago, and then it said like stuff like you know, like we're cooking
I think he's probably from from the New York or the East Coast or something. Exactly. That's why
I can say too, but I don't want to make you bad. You just said it cringes you so I'm not gonna do it
But yeah, that's how that's how I say it up to Sammy because I already know what he means by that. So
The same is cool. Do Sammy could do you got a lot of opinions? That's all I think he got opinions people take his opinions a little bit too serious
So
Easy he says like you what who to kick all the time like a baby in the whole and though. I don't believe he does hold on hi
No, no easy
Yeah, people are just
I just I sometimes I just read the comment and then I do that without like um, you know the sense of yourself
It's just like, you know, it's not true. I'm just saying yeah, it's just one of mine
It's another hate of it. I looked at the comments. It's all about easy
So yeah, they made it two days ago. I mean two years ago, but they just say
I don't know. I don't know this. I don't know volcano. So that's a new one for me
Okay, so guys guys. Can you just like behave yourself? I'll bring you back. But it's like
Something just monkeys, okay
So like, you know what thanks for having me back welcome back to the show guys
Thanks, I have one thing to say if you guys so much
Don't don't don't do it don't do it
Why do you why do you why do you why do you why do you why do you test my limit?
That's one rule you always have no matter what panel is you respect the host
My page disrespecting me goodbye band for life. I don't count any profiles. I'll reach I'll respect a I respect it
Yeah, I feel I feel too bad doing that and I should I need to like get over that like that feeling bad thing because it's like
I'm like I'm so into like
seeing every human being is like
No, you're too nice. You give everybody action chance even me like you know
Well, I mean it's a good one for him. People deserve a second chances because it's like we all make mistakes
It's like what's gonna happen? It's like, you know, no one's allowed to make a mistake and then
They're gonna have me but any people we're here to learn come on psyche
We have to go with the six I mean the six I made me just make up shit about me
I want to dress up the psyche, but I'm gonna keep it going just one person about this while you ended it
Would you mad I had your picture or?
Or it was all right. It didn't hurt you just a question run up with me here
He's tight. He's tight. You heard he's tight
Well, I mean the question is
Why you did that song?
Yeah
No, that's supposed to be a man. Why are you doing like that?
Right in the comments
That's him that's the real him
Right in the comments go to chat and say hi psych why why you scared?
No, I know it's the same person
What's what's wrong she's bought let me this day to be the same something no, ain't no wrong with the family
Why are you talking about beat it? What the fuck?
Comments
Okay
So she's drunk drunk tonight
Easy
Left what do you say I say that for a brother. That's a no you can say that he's
You know he was gonna get kicked so he said it in rain. Yeah, I know it's
Yeah, it's just a bit shit and so, you know, I told you I told you he's no good
He does he's gonna play a friend like he's
I'm telling you like you they don't like you over there. They may funny you they don't like would you care to meet me?
That's why when I went to beat like one of the last times I was in beat is like the time before last
I was our panel
I went to a chat and in the chat they're just talking all this shit like every letter. I knew everybody there
It's just some people over a month. I was like come on brother, and then he doesn't worry
They're talking all this shit about me and then like
Then it's like and then then then then made the mr. Big Pies incident. We're you ever heard this? I love you
Oh, I love you, too. Have you heard that either you ever heard that?
If nobody taught you today good job. Oh
I got you brother. I love you. We're gonna need to be it's your it's your fucking panel
It's your cheap. I have you were the heart on it
Okay, thank you
It's like yeah, I'm not buying my way in I'm make that nice and clear
I said I felt like blessing you cuz you might
You know
He's never demanded anybody off
I did spass the other night and said psyche don't put me on a one-on-one. I remember what I said
I remember
Hey, you know
Go
Either clone either brand my clone or fucking my me all them fucking clones of me
Okay, I'll make you say fuck you
You can't
What's the news, baby
What's happening? What's the word?
You heard
I don't see any comments yet. You need to comment. I'm going to talk. I'm going to talk. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
All right, it goes goes you hold it down. Hold it down. This is not the time for it
But you will be the god beef you'll be the god beef. Oh
That's not me brother
Yo, go hold it down. This is not the time. I just told you relax relax
No, I just I don't do no. I don't do nothing. I don't touch no. I don't touch like chat
I just
Odom damn clones. I don't want to incite penning the gayest
What are with you and be the what happened you and be the
Think we'll be you know
Every yeah
Earlier be those cooking diamond
My fault but I mean I mean yo if you don't see me blue is a fake me y'all could do all yet
Clones could do whatever y'all want the real me would be like he
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. It's gonna be you fucking
retards are talking. What's wrong, Samman? Ask for the
devil and he may appear. Why are you? Why are you all hyped up
for Samman? Relax. Chill papa. Alright, go ahead. The
wrong one. Oh, hold on. We're ready to demon. He's still on
the phone with you. I just took off my shirt cuz he's about
Where's your demons?
They just turned on the stove, some cooking was starting.
Mama, mama, mama, mama.
You don't know how to do scripts.
Let's run that bitch, dog.
I know how to do scripts and get on the people's skin,
but I'm not on here to talk about that.
Let's run it.
Let's talk about how you think that you're an email.
Let's beat us up.
You never will be.
That's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that's that
Imagine you saw you were a ball
You kicked around
Like
Like I was just trying to have a regular conversation to relax bitch you have a dick
You have a day and you set on it.
Okay.
The burden of proof was she made a claim or he made a claim.
Excuse me.
The burden of proof is on you.
Did I suck on it?
I pulled some of you jerking off on Twitter.
I don't give a fuck. You're jerking off.
Did I suck on it? You made the claim.
You're too stupid to even make the claim.
I don't give a fuck if you jerked off of that.
Did I suck on it? You fucking retard.
Go ahead. Make the claim.
Okay, the burden of proof.
Therefore, the burden of proof is on you.
I know it's boring. Let me bring this bitch up again.
It was so fascinating.
The burden of proof is on you.
You're too fucking stupid to have the conversation, correct?
No, you should just follow your Twitter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is silence.
Silence!
You're too stupid to have it.
Follow your Twitter and you're like, I need some flimsy down there.
You're also a fucking fraud.
You're a coward
It's true
You know better talk you never ever talk to big ghosts like that. You know what big ghosts do that
You know
Fuck you, let me handle. Let me handle it. Let me handle him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, let me handle him first
I'll get right back to you. Let me handle him first.
You're so triggered, girls.
You're so triggered by my presence.
It's funny. How about you?
If you're gonna have the debate or not, should I get to him?
You're so triggered by my presence.
You have a penis. Should I get to him?
We have a penis.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank
Yeah
Hold on
try to mute
Okay, yeah, so so flurry diamond just the other day like was like hey
My friend wants to get a reading and like you know, so
Started your whole fucking channel
I
Fucking channel
Vita your mic is messed up. I know and I know and I'm not I'm not I'm not you're all because you have
I didn't kick her I didn't kick her she's up. Okay, so let me just explain Vita, so I was uh, you know
Yes, you
Definitely helps
I will no she's left it around though. Let me explain. So, um, yeah, so
Lordy diamond like just like gave her you know told her friend about my show everything and that you asked
The employee diamond ever doing
So yeah, I consider that I consider that like helping my channel to me like you know
I'm bringing bringing people that when I get a reading and stuff. Okay, so
Okay, you know you you had to echo be that that's all I was saying be that had to go be that had the bat
Content site you got the I know
It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late. It's late
They'd stick audio and it will fix it
Be the mic always been good. I'm surprised you hear me. Yes. Yeah, you're gonna be done. Go ahead. You good
All right, thank you. Mm-hmm. How much money did you get from Florida darman? How much money did you get from me?
Did it get from from who?
You mean you'll meet a chair. I mean, I don't I don't
I mean, if you want to, um, you can actually include the dollar here. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you know, you, you spent more over a hundred, you know,
you know, donate well over a hundred dollars and 40 diamond, but 40 diamond, um, has, uh, did, did refer, uh, uh, like a client for like an hour.
I think we were doing that.
She referred to calling. Yeah.
Now, how many people have I brought here that give you donations?
All right
Are you scared? Are you scared of a fucking gritty diamond?
No, he's moving negative. No, I'm not scared.
Are you a coward?
Yeah, no, let me see.
Oh, let's put a chair on top. What about Tracy?
Yeah
People do you want to lose before you have to
I'll make you quit
i'll make you quit when i told you ld 15 is a sicko and you had him on the panel an hour ago
and i joined your panel and i said i'm sick of your fucking shit what'd you say you put me back
stage for ld fucking 15
Oh
Fuck you and your shit
Okay
There's something called standards and morals
How many times did you wait hold on hold on did you shut the fuck up you birthday fucking street walker
Did you have on your panels tonight or not
Did you have on your panel or not
I
Came up there, and I said get him up. What did you do you put him on solo and you kicked me off
On your panel or not
And did you put things like yeah, it's a kickoff right?
When I said why y'all talk about it
You asked me about soil and you said you put it on soil
Let's see what you write it's like
You said you want to see your money, your standard
You're not gonna get a penny from fucking Tracy
You're not gonna get any support from me
You don't, I don't give a fuck
Fuck your money is gone
You're trash too
I would never charge your channel
I would never be that close to me
I would never do that shit to you
I made your fucking channel
What do you think you want to be with Emma, huh? Okay, bye be there. Oh, wow, you kicked her
Okay, you kicked the site. No, I see
Suck you kicked it. I've seen it. It's like you kicked it
She's left it around
I think you're ready as I figure out the trigger. No, you had to figure now you pressed it. Nah, come on
So Tracy and I are on good terms like we were talking and discord
Yeah, he's calling me. He's just like you're like 20 20s doing call me trash
Like saying all these bad things. She has like the ex boyfriend or something. She was asking him about like, oh
Well, so sake is a fake reader, huh? And the guy's like
Yeah
Whoever's met hammer hammer and you ever seen hammer in the shot. That's my nigga right there
Hammers the favor hammer hammer. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Well, you say like that. Hey, what's up, huh? Whoa, sorry
Nine
Oh
No, my dad my dad used to say something he'd be like
Okay, okay, well you're pretty hard for saying that and you can just kick rocks. Okay, kick them. Who kick them like he's
That's just rude. You know, it's my father's my father's birthday. You know, he passed away last year, but it was birthday. Yes
Yeah
Yeah, anyway, oh my condolences site. Thank you
Yo, I feel your pain you're losing a parent is tough my condolences to you in your family, man
Yeah, or your father. Yeah, thank you and the players ain't on the play without I don't play with that at all, bro
I don't play with that at all
So if I was ever like talking back or something he'd go, okay
He's like I'm gonna count from 10 the 10 from 10 to one if you don't ever know or he's you know
He'd say every time you like every time you piss me off again, or he would say something back
I mean I add another point to get to 10 and then I don't even get to 10 points immediately
And then I get so mad. It would be maybe so mad. Sorry. I don't like to count the 10th thing
I'm not it's not set to me shoot. I don't
Tell them GTA 10 points motherfucker
Yeah, I'm not mad at you. I love you. I'm not mad at you. I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't
Welcome back site
When I'm around the drama the drama see it comes right back see it's been dead the drama is low when I'm around
I
Originally on earlier today she just happened and I and I knew of a script to really get under her nerves, so
Yeah
Oh here she is home
This is not it's a speed up
Yeah, I'm you muscle with that cook up. No, no, no someone want to talk to you for a second. Okay. I'll leave the panel. I'll leave the panel
You too you leave to garbage
Let that fucking has freak off some of public platform. All right, but you're the fucking like a man
You give full body for a hundred dollars to fucking like men and Chuck
Like I
Nobody wants to talk to you garbage
Except you take up you're taking leftovers go go suck some raging demon dick
You know what because my hole is not that fucking loose, okay?
But your asshole is a woman that knows how to take care of her.
Your asshole is big enough to care for her.
So anyway, Samad, what I wanted to tell you,
let me tell you where this dirty bitch came from.
She actually got mad because I was like,
she said I was a supporter of you.
Remember that?
Samad, get your fucking asshole over here right now.
Because I don't want to hear this fucking
pinko brain fucking bitch talking.
And you're fucking dumb.
That's all where everybody had the link. Do you think this is the best push-up like what is the picture that you have?
With diamond now, that's a crazy beat
I just want to tell you do you remember when fucking flirty diamond turn on me
It was because she said that you doctor right under your channel. She turned on me
She wanted like that stupid flirty. What is that flirty demon?
You're a stupid slut. That doesn't know how to have a fucking freak off
For reaching demon to get over me
It's really the salmon. Would you rather have a freak off with me or flirty diamond?
No, I'm gonna ask him
No salmon go ahead. I like to see you push you which one do you want do you want to see me or flirty diamond?
I like to see you push y'all. That's all I'm gonna. All right. Let's ask easy easy. Would you like to if you weren't married?
Oh
Why you position like that
Like in your picture to watch you back. Why do you like can you put on like solo with that slot on solo?
Like you why are you position like that?
Are you taking a selfie of yourself and like trying to have a
And guess what the guys on the panel including psyche would rather still be with me
You're
Not that big be the be the be the you naked backstage or a you stuff
Doesn't matter what I do all the man would rather be with me though, and you think I carry I'm older than you to
I'm way older than you. I'm way older than you. I'm not a they still rather be
That's the thing. I don't need my love out male validation
At all yes, you do that's why I put it on boss on you. That's what you did
You keep saying oh raising them and none of these guys want you raging demon would rather be with me
Raging demon is thirsty of raging demon cried over me
Raging demon cried over me
Okay
Yeah, he cried over me you cried over him multiple times still not a whole ass man
Yeah, I asked that one more time.
You know, you're a full spot.
Yeah, who would say you're a full spot?
On your desk, Brad, and you need any attention you can get,
and you have a big desk, and nobody wants it.
Peter, why are you here? I got a serious question.
Why the fuck are you here?
You're a slut.
You're a fucking new sub-slut that likes people.
Nah, she ain't a slut. She's a fucking new sub-slut.
So as a street walker, when I was your age,
I already had a fucking degree.
What'd you do? Walk in the fucking streets?
I'll kill you now. Yeah, you got to pick me up.
I'm feeling a crush on you. Oh, Kali's cat is in a, Kali's cat is in a chat.
What I just run this bitch
It might be a man that wants to be a woman beta, but you're fucking you join here all the time
You were such a little fucking squirmy little bitch. So you said I'm gonna count
You joined three times now, you know, you want to know who made Psyche, do you know I was actually before Psyche?
Do you know when your dad was doing his tests, it's called BKG, because I actually was the one, like, I brought up.
We don't need you now.
Where'd you come from?
Bye bye.
Psyche.
Thank you. Thank you. Do you want me to come?
How'd you find psyche?
I heard you find psyche.
I'm sorry.
I heard about you.
I hear you talking about everybody on this fucking channel.
80 percent of them are here because I'm sorry.
It's because of me.
Salman, how'd you find psyche?
Not through you.
Don't fuck.
Salman.
I typed in open panel on YouTube. I didn't ask you. Salman. How'd you find sake you?
I mean if it's 80% you probably should I didn't ask you.
You're not salmon. Salman. How'd you find fucking sake you? Nobody wants to talk to you. You already count it down.
You're already realized how many times you're gonna start to leave again leave bitch. We don't care
That's all by you beta salmon. How'd you find psyche by you be?
Can you pull up your shirt and show your chest to this mother fucker fuck up. It's my tattoo on his
head. He got a tattoo on me. Can you shut the fuck up?
All right
Every single one of you
So, you know, did you know that Saipi the channel holder has a tattoo on my name on his chest?
Yeah, I know that I know that I know that's what they want. Why are you gonna tell me to get the fuck out of here?
Not you, not you. I want to kick you. I want to kick you, but you know
Long be the was calling for me. I was in the kitchen making
Man, that's a long time ago. No one was calling for like two minutes
If it was a long time ago is because I don't give a fuck. What do you have a tattoo that says fucking channel?
I made you didn't make shit, bitch. That's who we have to
You start cleaning. I have a tattoo
I have a tattoo
Yeah, we're cuddling. Well now you're bringing up personal shit. You shouldn't do that
I'm not
do that you dumb fuck but you're too much you're too much of a retard to even have that conversation
you're a geron that proof is in oh and you're a fucking dumb ass fucking whore
You don't the fuck you're talking about you're gonna make
Yeah
Let's run that bitch
and I should be very important fuck off bitch nobody cares once you count down again you're
I gotta tell two of you and I should be very very very important all right go shut the fuck up
nigga damn hey she ain't gonna fucking you fucking white knight yeah i don't give a fuck i just want
to hear the content nigga you're not the content but your background noise and it's just stupid
and you're a fucking man
You're fucking that right now.
Imagine the Nike 50 on when you should show your tattoo.
Show his loyalty.
Show your loyalty, Psyche.
There you go. There you go, Psyche. Perfect.
Perfect.
Show your loyalty, Psyche.
Show your loyalty.
Show your tattoo.
For your tattoo you bitch ass. What what does that say? It says BKG. That's my name bitch, okay?
That's all I have to say
I got that I never get a tattoo of you ha ha ha flirty diamond. I don't want him to get a tattoo of me actually
Your trash
One-but-cheek and
You'll be on one cheek
You're a man lurking as a woman taking other people's like so-called voice rats.
Diamond be on his cock
Raging diamond? Raging diamond.
That's a good day. Raging diamond. Wow, I love it. Raging diamond.
You're such a dirty whore, where you literally make the same fucking mess.
You sell your whole body for 100 to men.
Like you literally change, like you don't ever change this fucking dildo, you don't ever fucking
Clean and you just put that dirty
Disgusting
Yeah, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all be friends, we're supposed to all
I'll send it to you, Salma.
What?
There should be no dig.
We don't need to make no flow.
Eldos send it to me.
No, no, no.
I don't know.
I'll send it to you.
I think, I think Spike has already seen it though.
I haven't seen it.
You want to say it? Can I see it? Can I watch it? Can I watch it? I won't share it. Okay. I'll send it to you right now. Okay?
It's on Twitter. Oh, so she said she says she don't give a fuck if anybody sees it.
That's it. That's it. I heard her. You heard that too, right Sammy? I heard you. You heard that, right? She okay if nobody passed her pitches around. I heard it. I don't care. You want to see my porn so bad. I don't give a fuck.
No, dummy don't give a fuck.
I put the shit out of that.
You don't want to have any you complain about it ever as you said it.
I'm just saying. Oh my god. It's all my Twitter me sucking dick is on Twitter. I really know
I don't want to see it, but I don't want to. I don't want to hear you complain about it. All right
So bad
I don't want to see a dick sucker. It's perfectly fine. You can suck dick all you want on film is okay, but I
It's okay. I'm nobody said I'm feeling on film
When you watch the video I want to see I want to see you on full screen cuz I want to see your reaction
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Okay, I don't I don't see I don't see I think there's a pillow or something covering the
It's like you don't know what's down there. You don't know what's down there. So it's like it's a mystery
You asked for it though, Flirty, you said I could share it, I gave it to Psyche, and you were correct.
I gave it to your permission, and I named it to Psyche.
You said I should send this to Saiki.
Thank you. Thank you. You enjoy that shit?
I can't now. I don't care.
You like dick with chicks?
I don't care.
Fuck you. Fuck you, bitch.
It's like a surprise. It's like a fun surprise.
Saik, why you scream like that? It was big.
Because I thought it was a real life.
It was like you see it was like so like the mirror like it was like she's petty like a kitty in the pillow
And I was like what did she pay and then it's like the almost in the pillow is gone and it's just like whack whack in it
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I don't have a dick to fucking like whack off.
Like, I don't have a dick to walk off or anything.
Who literally have access to my dick.
And I guess what?
I don't need money.
I'm not like a dirty, thirsty bitch, with a dick.
That's the thing.
You're an e-slut.
When I was your age, I already had a dick.
I'm still catching my breath.
You're an e-slut, Bita.
Look at, look at, just Psyche's reaction was priceless.
It was a comic call.
I'm still catching my breath, Bita.
Nobody wants to see anybody wants to see it with her permission
All right
like I just said I thought it was I thought it was be careful she might get hurt and strike your
channel I'm selling I'm selling the backstage freak off videos of you
How many of you men want to see a guy fucking jerk enough how many tickets are gonna be
You're tickets are gonna be fucking like nobody wants to buy that show and the freak off
Your
Dive
You should have shut your mouth, okay
That's love but you're jerking off and you're walking the street and you're look at your
Well your backstage and you're a man
And you're a slut and you have a used up twat bitch a hairy
You're still a man you have a hairy fucking twat bitch
Like everybody saw your hair
They had to do that.
And they enjoyed it.
That's me.
They had to do it.
What did you say?
What did you say, man?
I didn't get up.
Listen.
A lot of these men would rather have hair on a pussy
than a fucking dick with no hair.
Pussy.
Damn.
Backstage for free you showed your hairy ass pussy. Well me I got paid. Why are you cracking? Are you gonna cry again?
Bitch
Even if I was the hairiest bitch ever all I gotta do is shave it off and laser off. What are you gonna do with your dick?
I'm gonna have sex with your daddy
Turn it
Don't come on listen and then she's gonna strike your channel for what she said
Every stream now
Lurdy diamond that just like introduce a new friend. I'm maybe a supporter
Let me tell you one thing let me tell you
Flip out you crash out any moment someone mentioned staging demon
Raging demon. Oh my god
Thank you do your best raging demon impression like every time I'm raising diamond right beta raging diamond
I'm quitting YouTube. I can't take it anymore. I love you. I love you be a
Oh
I will always be writing together for life. So what are you gonna do? You always have a dick
What not really?
I'm sad. Can you bring your up your channels in the back traffic? Oh, make sure I'm some to your shits. I
Got you
I'm trying to roll some weed up like you're literally stupid. Like I'm literally having
I
Can send you my new pussy this year. Don't worry. I was in it. I was in it too for free cuz we're both slots. Don't worry
When you go
Nobody wants to see your new pussy. What are you talking about cuz you're saying I won't have a pussy ever
I'm gonna show you I'll send it to you for free
I'm gonna send it to for free
I would have promised Tracy X and you now a free video of me after I have bottom
Thank you, please don't violate us with that horrific fucking image. No way I'll send it to you. No, thank you
No, it's okay though, baby.
If you've done this to me, you're actually like traumatizing me.
Even that shit felt like a horror film.
Just having to hear that shit felt like a horror film.
And you're gonna send that to Tracy too? Fuck your fucking bitch, fucking bitch.
I said Tracy X, dumbass, hoe.
What the fuck is that?
I told Tracy X this fucking like a month or two ago, actually.
What's Tracy? There's two Tracy's. Nobody wants to see that shit, okay? Save it for a freak show, okay?
Save it for the fortune.
Because Tracy next time I go into a little fight and I told her I'll send her a video of my new pussy this year.
And now I'm going to send you one too, Betta.
Jesus.
I don't know you guys got you
To say that she was like a man disgusting like he would
And now I defended her and you know what fucking she said I have messages I have messages for her saying I
Would never ever ever fucking respectate raging human
He said the worst things to you because he said he would fuck my mother's grave
He said he holds my cast die on my fucking laugh
I said the worst of the worst to me and you said you
He called you PDFs didn't he?
What's the proof didn't yeah, I don't need proof
Did he not call you most disgusting shit?
All right, so keep on making excuses from your fucking
I'm not ready to demon be the rage is with diamond now
Like
I'm in diamond is not lying beta. I've seen the got the screenshot
Psyche
Raging demon call you bad names like PDFs. Nobody's bad. Nobody's bad. Everybody's this massive bearer. It's not a mod
Right now it's like a little faggot get on panel and talk about it
Yeah
I'm trying to draw a man you call black or a G of PDF
That's the wrong word psyche so if anybody but what has to do with anything now. I'm trying to draw me
I'm just asking beta. He's got a lot to do with everything because somebody that's supposedly was my friend
Slurdy diamond all the sudden finds it
I kicked you psychic you off the panel for LD. He's your friend. I think he's
He's he's he's he left at her. Oh, right. I didn't kick off the panel
She asked me and she also asked me to put his photo. Oh, she's put him up full screen. Let's have a look at let's say
That's what you like you bitch. That's what she says
You guys can rewind and you can see it. I mean if you have to I would never say put them on full screen
So you're dammit, I saw an armpit, I saw some kind of armpit.
Two hours, two hours, almost two hours, almost two hours.
Raging demon with flirty.
She was like on the phone with six hours.
Raging demon, where do you see that?
You don't want to be sucking on flirty.
Right now with diamond, let's go, fuck, beat up.
My pimps, raging demon, sucking on flirty.
Yikes.
Oh
bring the um chat back bring the back chat back come on flirty okay come on you have any exposed it come on you have any exposed it come on flirty come on flirty you have any exposed it come on flirty come on
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
come on flirty come on you have any exposed it up in it right now you just bro you just run the best concept right now come on bro i was a little bit
That's a little better than psyching speedos. Come on now. Come on now. Let's go
Yo, you be psyche right now with that little content with that
That's content right there. I already showed it
Doesn't feel be the hot doesn't feel
Rage of demons gonna diamond damn be the what you did to him because he left he went
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
raging demon and really, really pathetic for fucking flirty
diamond. That's how I feel. You're jealous? Absolutely not.
You think you think I couldn't get you think I couldn't get
raging back? I'm gonna call them raging cocking out raging
demon raging demon was in love with me. He cried and why you
can't put why diamond why you can't give me an update picture
though. God damn.
Because that's my favorite photo of you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Favorite one, you fucking.
That's my favorite photo of this time, man.
Watch where Rage of Demons throw acid in the face.
Contest, contest.
I'll be in the back.
Rage didn't go through.
I don't know if that was a real Kate in the chat.
Because it is.
Damn!
How many pinkies are out of me?
Yo, who the hell is that?
That make a cool.
He look cool.
He look cool as you.
Scribe to that guy.
Subscribe to that guy. You heard subscribe
Man
That's good content, baby. That's good content. Yeah, that's great content. Yeah, um, you're not mad, right?
All right, we go to you. All right, subscribe to Sammy
Nigga, that's nigga. You know how how how many times that picture got passed around
All right, then we go to you we go to y'all here subscribe to Sammy
You think that like that's how she got the fucking like screenshots. She's up test
I'm not mad
That's right, look at that.
Diamond, come on, are you making fun of Psyche?
Oh, Psyche's making fun of you.
I'm going to make fun of someone that literally just
showed me screen shot some turtle from Squirtle Turtle.
I was thinking she'll bury the butt in a wiener photo,
but I heard that I'm in real.
Shout out shout out shout out shout out to the June team. You know buddy. No, buddy
And try to strike your
Maybe trying to make you spin fast to be to be the fucking east lot
Uh, shout out to somebody trying to take your channel down so I can.
Well, I think, I don't like, she, like, she didn't really understand, like, the flagging with, like, you know.
I'm actually calling me a slut when you get paid walking the streets.
I'm a whore, not a slut.
What?
There's a big difference.
Oh
Fish, I can be standing like everywhere and that would be great for you, okay?
Yeah, you're a post-op trainer.
Yeah, I'm a post-op trainer and I got nice tips. You got a dip.
Yeah, you're a post-op trainer. You have the surgery. I know.
You have the surgery ready.
I'm okay. All right. I'm post-op now.
Exactly. That's what Alex came in saying the other day and he was like,
but he was like, I was like, Alex, it's ridiculous.
And he was like, really like saying over and over and over.
I got a good question. I got a good beat up beat up. I thought it was Haram to have a hairy bush
I'm a diamond and diamond say you shit. It's Harry Bush. That's I guess. Yeah
Good question. Good question. It's also Haram to be a prostitute with a dick walking around the streets. Oh
Wives and that would never accept you bitch. Nope. Don't she got no
While you just sit around to make food for him bitch
Huh, that's not like, you know, that's words like, you know
A bunch of fucking wipes and shit making multiple foods because he doesn't just want new he wants a bunch of fucking women and shit like we so thrilled
No, I mean, be for real, be for real, yard hut, yard hut.
There's things that are in cultures that we think are weird that are just totally insurmountable in those cultures.
It's not bombing places.
I know, I'm just hiding.
I'm bombing places. Yeah.
Wow.
Okay. Let's not get it. Let's not get it.
Let's not get it. Let's not. Let's not.
Let's not. Let's not.
Let's not get it.
Let's just stop
Hey, nobody wants raging demon besides you and he wants you to best of luck
I love you guys get I hope you get married and you fucking swap dicks all night long
Don't forget to make a video. Don't forget to make a video. Put it on.
Exactly.
Don't forget to make a video. Put it on.
Imagine thinking I would be jealous. You should pick better men. I should get jealous.
No, no. If you got a curl under your neck, I would be a little jealous.
Yeah, if you could get a curl, I would be a little intimidated.
Why you haven't went live on a date yet?
Yeah, we have.
What's the noise he's in another continent
Clubs he can't go he's too busy owning club. He's C. I
I have my dentures
Hello
Who is that? Who is that?
Is he? Is he at his view?
Is he making all those weird noise?
Were you the one moaning earlier?
What are you talking about?
No, no, no, no, definitely wasn't me.
I promise she's psyche. That was not me.
That wasn't me.
In my chest.
On the panel.
On that level.
like he's got girls
oh that's flirty diamonds like dakin uh dima got you
they got your picture beat up god they're you oh my god
where where where where i didn't see it i didn't see it
should we choose on flirty diamond pictures
damn oh she's a wicked witch yeah i know somebody
well my wicked witch is barbra so yeah
I
Pictures like
Guess what's not AI your dick being waxed off in your house
And you would know cuz you fucking have to rub your pussy to everything. I'm sorry people
It's getting a little bit explicit.
It's getting a little bit explicit, too.
We'll come and take it back.
Take it back.
Take it down a notch.
Come on.
That's our arm.
You can't beat.
You can't.
Psyche is going to throw up if he watches what he just saw again.
You can't flick the beat.
Oh, my God.
You're going to hear how he screamed?
Oh my god, I can't get that sound on my head.
Psyche is going to throw up if he watches what he just saw again.
That's what I thought is how I didn't think she was if she was going to show it.
I thought I was going to cover it and then I was like glanced back down.
It was just like all out.
It was like it's out.
He actually was crazy.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
You said it.
You said show it.
You said you're such a psycho.
Yeah, he's like surprised at all.
That was funny.
I was a paid whore.
Even a psyche didn't like your dick.
Psyche likes dick and he's almost barf.
So I like I like my I like my dick on like a hairy ass. I like a man
Yo, what I'm doing. Come on, bro. Well, I do. I mean, I don't like it. I don't like I don't like I don't like all
female
read it read it read it read it read it read it full screen and then read it
you solid advice i was gonna say no put it right there read it read it again
you read it can you read it said horrible things but you called you a man and a pdf
i was hurt and asking private why don't know why you're so mad i'm your hate while we're raging
What I say, that's so bad and how long was that? Wait, wait, months ago.
What's so bad about that?
What is so wrong with that? Like, what's so wrong about reaching out to you,
what I do to you? I didn't cry.
I mean, you know exactly what that whole message said.
Can somebody screenshot it?
Yeah, show it again. Show it again.
Somebody so it again wait wait come on. Come on. No videos. Oh, oh
How much I fought for you with very I was told I always told you I'm here for you
I never put you down. Maybe it's me any excuse not to like me and that's why I say best which was just to you
And then it shows and why and what is that? Am I explode? What am I saying?
You're what is what what is the big exposure?
I'm raging a mod up in here. You're crying about me making raging a mod. Where am I crying?
in the chat right here.
What do you say?
Right here. She sent me a screen shot of raging demon being a man and then I know what is the next message?
And then she said I sent you a screenshot how much I fought for you with Barry
I always told you I'm here and I never put you down
Maybe it's me in this is not to like me and that's why I say best wishes to you diamond
You literally got so triggered over raging being a model. You sent me a private message
I can you read what else I wrote where he called you a pedophile and a man
I said I thought you hated him but but but
fuck everybody and everybody that stood up for diamond you are sending out our messages now
I never asked you about my demon nor offered you money to sell the trip because I consider you friends offended you
Alright, let's get on my discord now
Let's get on my discord now
I said horrible things about you called you a man
Should we hear your mind to score my messages?
There's five messages to be
It is the point where we're so mad and you're hated to do that
You can mod like you love me
Never asked you to not mod anybody
But yet here you were and sent me
Okay, go now go to your messages go up go farther
And then I showed you and then you message we talked briefly on the 12th over the alex situation
And I showed you this concept, baby
And I
I mean take a picture that take a picture
Let's watch hours now. I'm a block 30 minutes turn into two hours
Do you realize that I actually blocked that guy like month like five months ago
She's doing he's doing the phone with oh my god. He's still on the phone. What are you doing imagine?
He's on the phone with him
Oh
Yeah, they're talking about me
He doesn't have like like blonde curly hair
Okay, that's it
Okay, listen already diamond takes leftovers from like friends of hers
And you're a street whore with a dick you're a flat you're a flat way you have no
Look at your fucking profile picture. You never said you were reaching you said reaching was never your boyfriend's
Let's go
So, therefore, there's never any leftovers. They were eating
He cried over me
Talked to him for four months. He loves me a good guy, but I can't be with him
He gets manic haven't spoken for six months plus. He's very nice compared to him
Wait, who is that about?
I am fun. Where's your foundation? Who was that about?
Yo, diamond with the DM. It wasn't about fucking rating you man. Thank you
Don't forget Kate wouldn't have your number it wasn't for Barry. I'm gonna zoom in and clean it out
Okay
And you guys see that you see what he's showing right? Wait till she's done with everything she's showing and then I'll show my shed
We're gonna cook really good we're gonna cook
That was Ricky Ricky. No, that's a Ricky late. That's a Ricky Ricky. Shout out to be this whole channel.
Yo, how many? Shout out to be this old channel. Wow. Did you the one that took it down? You have to take it down with it.
That's how you help take it down with this. How she had things private. Let's see what's in conspiracy people.
It's just shout out to be this old channel. Shout out to be this old channel. Shout out to my new channel that gets more viewers than you.
Bitch, because I'm not gonna fuck like you.
I'm gonna eat you.
Bitch, because I got more fucking going for me than you.
People like to watch me, even though you're fucking a skank in the street.
You only get 10 viewers.
Thank you, my boo.
Only don't even don't even know oh wait with this
Listen flirty diamond, I'm gonna play the message of you crying
What did I say you're beautiful
Like you's awake and Sarah's cooking bitch
Hit the like subscribe get all notifications
Listen, you already been cooked you spent six hours Michael linguine you spent six hours with Michael linguine and now you're with
Shout out to Tracy my girl. Shout out to Tracy. Shout out to Tracy
Shout out to Tracy. Shout out to the Tracy shout out to Michael linguine shout out to
Bring it back. Bring it back. Whoever's playing that record is bring it back. Bring it back. We're listening to
You're going to get all the messages that you really need to hear.
You want to hear me cry? There you go. All right. You want to hear me cry? I'll play the clip.
What
You were crying earlier when fucking Alexander was fucking
That's you talking man
You're a man and you're talking like a man
Yeah, we're gonna play you crying
I'm gonna let you drain yourself and I'm gonna do everything that needs to be shown
I can just play towards me and really stood out.
Drop your diamonds now, diamond.
Drop your diamonds now, because the gold is coming to take over.
Sorry, but don't let people join if they ain't going to put the cash in there.
He really gained my respect that day because...
You gained my respect that day. That's what she's saying to me though.
And I don't know whether you're exposing yourself or it's me. It's disgusting. You know, they just generally want to fuck me because
In my practice, I didn't know him, but at the same time, it's not right how...
Yeah, I was tied on the Arnold Kibbida.
So you're talking about how I defended you?
It's self-exposure, whatever it is. Let it be done. Let it be heard. Let it be heard.
Except for me defending you and being nice to you.
Something was coming up. Something was coming up.
When I've done absolutely nothing to these people.
I don't care if these men feel like I tricked them or not, and they never would have slept with any of these men.
I'll just step off, you heard? So that's the content.
Okay, Sam, watch it.
No, Sammy, Sammy, chillin'. Sammy, chillin'.
Sammy, chillin'.
You're livin'.
I'm chillin'.
I'll be watchin'.
I gotta take care of this guy.
I said leave all the content.
I'm leaving.
Come on, baby.
There's no business with what's going on with me.
Don't talk to us.
Now here you go fuck it up if you stay here site don't let nobody else
Don't hear me cry. No, that's not what we're gonna play
No, that's all we're gonna play. I don't know what you're playing right now
But the shit I have on you bitch, you're gonna be crying. No, I'm gonna cry beat us
So I don't know what you're playing right now. I don't know what you're playing
What would you play what would you play flirty? What would you play? I have no idea
I could get an understanding what's going on like what would you play who messes with that?
It's her talking
Thank you, thank you. She's talking shit about you over here
What can I say about tracing any capacity and I just didn't say anything I just I did it but you know
And that's just why raging why fucking games like a lot of respect for him and all you have to say
You don't care about Tracy. You don't care about psyche, but you have respect for raging demon
Who fucking turned me on my life you and I you're disgusting
What's that shit that you got let's see how much you don't want to get exposed
Let's see that shit that you got
Let's see the shit that she's hiding
Let's say that she's having
You know, she just literally talk shit on her so explain my point of view, but all you had to say was your point of view
Sounded like you're fucking talking shit about everybody. I
Wasn't talking shit about no one I was yes, you did you said you don't like psyche
You don't like fucking Tracy and you don't fucking like
So you got to listen.
Let me tell you one thing because, you know, you try to strike
psyche channel for what?
Because you didn't like the way Alex talks to you.
You could have left have no car.
I don't have a car.
You know, I'm saying I try to take down the panel.
No car to fucking cars are paid for.
And I have a fucking no cards to play.
It is like you should try to get more fucking shit up to play.
I just had a video put on a restriction.
Yeah, that's why you're lying now. So what is your card reaching demon? I
Got you all mad right now about reaching actually you're crashing out over him
Girl, you're making me fucking giggle.
Let me tell you, let me tell you, Raging Demon is the one person
that got dumped so hard, you have to come and cry on psyche's
panel about me many times over and over on my birthday.
On May 6th, he came over and beat up, beat up.
Everybody knows Raging Demon melts over me.
He loves me on your personal panel.
So you're just like a little like rag, a little wet rag that he
uses to wipe himself off because he wants to like
to get me jealous. You think I give a fuck about that guy?
Are you sure? Are you sure? Are you sure?
Are you sure? Hey, I psyche, what do you think?
Was raging demon crying over me or not a psyche?
Are you sure that he's using me to get you jealous, Kira?
I don't know. Maybe you're using yourself to get some attention.
Shut up the psyches. Awake in service. Hit the lights.
Maybe you're using each other to get attention.
I don't give a fuck.
No, you do.
Listen.
You clearly carry me.
Yeah, he has a nice big loads that he does raking semen a lot of big loads come out of that. Oh god. Oh gross
I want to fucking die right now. This is nasty
Dude next Robin and against each other exposure today
Don't you beat up you love that you sound like you love stuff like that. Do you miss being do you miss being pre-op beta?
You miss being pre-op
What does that mean? You're discussing. What would I like to be raging?
So, you know, you're calling. She's saying you're saying before operation like we play. Yeah.
Yeah. You're still on the phone with him, right? It's more than three hours.
Oh, I had an operation. You're still on the phone. A bit more than three hours, people.
Are you okay?
Like, you know, you know, you know, do you miss when you're a pre-op?
How would you not know a medical terminology like that?
Because I never I don't know because I've never been through it
No, we have a low people are saying you're tranny and people are saying on your post-op now, so
So it's pretty pretty damn pretty diamond when you go to the gynecologist and put your legs up in the stirrups
Like what is there? What is their face when they?
We got a colleges
No, what is it? What is it? What is it the guy called his face when he lifts up the sheet?
Like you know, like I'm just asking like, you know, do you miss being like pre-op you miss it?
I'm
Real woman, you know, I want to know how many perry is flirty hat. I
Think she's like absolutely fucking delusional
I missed the pre-op, I feel like he had proof of you being pre-op.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, I do, I miss being pre-op.
What are you talking about?
Okay, I'm a pre-op, or what are you talking about?
Yeah, I miss it so much, that's why I did it.
I miss it, I want to go back to being you with a dick.
I think Alex is a little bit of a not-perfect source.
I mean, Alex, I don't know if he has some theories.
You're gonna fall, if you fall, if you fall, Alex's theories will fall down the rabbit hole, and maybe we'll never be able to get, guys, just be careful, I believe, you're gonna think that, you know, we're all, the entire panel is just beat on a voice changer, like.
Hit the Alex theories, don't worry, sometimes he's, sometimes he's close, but sometimes, you know, he's always wrong, but.
It's quite elaborate. It's quite elaborate thing. He just has he sees like, you know, there's discord Brigade, you know
What's her name?
Brains in charge of it. God. He's just like the errand boy of it
Like, you know, like they're working with it and then they're all these other other people like that are on the show for months
That's a true story. Yeah, psyche
You know, do you know AC?
AC this guy AC was on the
On the panel tonight. I forgot to ask him a question though. He said he I think no
I didn't know you though. He said he met through bronze birds, but he came over here, and he was like
Paras oh he's like, you know flurry diamond had him on our altercation to his name gates
It was AC does he do know who AC is like he was he's a streamer
He's a streamer, and I think I might know him from somewhere else
I might know from I know another I know a couple AC's
But I don't know if he was an interesting guy. Um, but he's like Hispanic, but then he said he said beat
He's he said be a any are like over and over and over again
I kind of like the Tony people used for the n-word bomb and so I ended the stream and he's like I'm nice again
I'm like, well, it's okay. It's like I just don't like to have the words said like that on the show
You can talk about like
Exactly you guys know, okay to
Just he beat a home. Don't come on midnight midnight never has nothing nice to say
Alistair's expose days are hilarious. Oh, yeah, it's the right of the different Alex
The agreement Alex Alex McQueen like he has yeah, he has some theories like, you know, oh, yeah, it's expose days. Yeah
You know
Everybody's everybody
Midnight, are you okay midnight? I crash it out midnight. It's always a set is that a cat Williams avatar you have
Are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are
That's really funny. She's fucking she can't accept the truth right now
She can't accept the truth. Why would I lie about something like this?
So what do you re-incuse of lineup?
She's saying that I that the whole raging thing. It's fake and I'm lying about raging
Break down break it down like break it down while from the beginning man. No, she can't accept it
Well, she can't accept
She can't send anything regarding raging and I told her I was on the phone
She's accusing of the phone call between Reggie and I being fake
She's saying that the phone calls fake, you know, Sam already told her they're very much on the phone with each other
So you still on the phone with him right now?
Maybe maybe not
I
Don't know why would she say that some people say it and some people, you know
Even showed you his wiener yet
He's so I mean she'll be in a picture. He said I think she was she was he was shocked
But what were you do you think a picture of it or show you video? Have you done have an e-sex?
I never seen the video that they're talking around psyche
Have you had an e-sex with them I already have plenty of freak off the raging
Jesus are you drinking off to you?
Virgin can buzz fat loads multiple times. Oh my god
He jerked off and he jerked off and busted multiple times. Wow
Say words never say word
Well, that's it's a good thing. It seems she meant is good for milk production. So maybe it will help out so from
Fram from Michael is very raging demon you always take leftovers from you know, she never claimed them
So it's not leftovers because she never claimed them
But she just said I could never have raging and now she's in the comments saying that complete opposite clock that
I thought the truth like
Are you planning to meet
And nobody wants those fucking
Flirty flirty are you planning to meet region demon is you in America? We already met you already met
Yeah, you went to England
You lying
Oh my god, you did a full worldwide. They went they did a worldwide tour. I mean they went to England and California
They they actually they both bought round trip tickets, and then they both missed each other
Oh, the way they're back
I'm sorry. Hey, um
No, he's in England. He's in England. I think I don't know
30 don't don't don't throw the cap in the air give it a buck. Yeah, we already married
I saw the photo of us kissing ready. Well, you met y'all met up in the hotel you smashed what happened
If you make a photo in the same place you made the Christine and summer photo
So you met up you went to the hotel. Did he take you out to eat like how many days I spent together? I need details. I
like details
Yeah, let's get to the sex how is the sex
Come on wait, I was gonna get there, but let's let's get the little things first. Okay. It's like he rushed to it
So who's the top who's the top who's the bottom I wanted I want to know the logistics
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Maybe maybe I hopefully will all like be able to like work things out and like you know. Oh
My god, she be she be that's enough in an inappropriate comment. It's his boy. Oh my god
Yeah, I think I'm gonna call the busty they call it a busty is like a more appropriate name called or busty or busty. I don't know
This he has sex with the OT I don't know
But but but oh yeah, he does go on already. I told you the story, but what happened last night and everything right? Yeah
I told this story so
But I did yeah, the moral story is that I did see the guy's dick last night and
He like really you wanted me to see it apparently because he's like had it already
Well, I mean, it's like I wonder what would have happened if I would have like just kind of go down in front of his girlfriend
But that not a little bit too shy. I have to be invited. So I just said it's I just looked at it and I say hey
You're looking pretty buff
The other guy with the black with the pink background
Hold on the guy left the last night no the guy from last night
No, I'm talking about the guy the guy that actually came to my house last night. Do you hear the story?
Yeah, like I was I was doing my show and he came over and he's like hey, he's like hey
Do you want to watch me?
F my
F this chick or something like that. He's like, you just have to give me like a DMT like a little um a
Cord or like a power cord from my DMT my DMT we get smoked DMT and like hang out
So we went and we're 711 we came home and then I was like, oh, yeah
It's like I think people say that before like oh, yeah
We could watch it every day and they never let me do but then he like left the door open
But then I still like didn't come in because then he didn't like call me in
And so then I, uh, and then he did, but then he eventually did call me in and he was like,
they're both like laying there naked on top of the bed, like, and, uh,
and he was completely aroused and, uh,
Yeah, then I spoke some DMT. I got so fucking, um, lit. Oh my god. It was just like crazy. And then I,
Wow. Whoa. Psych. You got lucky last night.
Let me tell you, I mean, I, I, I even, even seeing a dick is good luck to me at this point. You know, as I, as I, as I, so
It's pretty funny though. Yeah.
It's gonna mess this home. It's going on. That's 440 already. I was going fast
Mmm, they left the door open so I can hurt it all. Yeah doors wide open. Oh
Yeah, I mean I heard yeah, cuz then I heard her like oh
It's not like tonight on the panel. Let me bet maybe this this I'm ever just having reverberations from where I heard
Yeah, she was making some stuff and it's like it it sounded like you're like
He's slapping and like a suctioning sound and then just like screaming and then and then he called me
Yeah, so I knew it was already was all over the time. I got him
No, no, but she was she was like so he was like laying on the bed like kind of like
Like unlike the back at the near the back of the bed like kind of like laid out
Like it's just like and then like oh and then she was like with her butt up in the air like on her stomach or something a little bit
She looks like a vegan Patriot. Yeah, she looks like a she looks like a brunette vegan Patriot
I can't show your picture or tell you about her, but she does he let me she has that very like a vegan patriot
Um
And or he was watching porn. It's like he did. Yeah, I did not touch. Okay, see
Yeah
But he's really cute though the guy's really he's blonde hair blue eyes like he's like tall like muscular like
No, I don't think they made a record but you know, maybe next time they'll ask me that because he seems like he's like
He seems like he's like he was like just like making jokes afterward like every before they left that he was making jokes
He's like, oh, I'm leaving you for a man. I like I liked it
I like to say all this stuff. So it's kind of funny. I dated a woman back. Yeah, I did be able to back down
What's a random three?
That's a random 5k to have sex in your home. Why would someone random?
Ass have sex in your home you why should you let someone?
What the fuck well kind of kayak okay? I don't be there the story kind of because I'm attracted to him and
You know I'm using them around. Yeah, I've done it for years. I've done it for years and he's never
Never said anything like this before
I want you to put on mute and listen to the messages that Florida diamonds sent to me
Including the screenshots that she sent to me trying to take your channel down
You send me fucking videos of Alexander
All right psyche can analyze for himself
It's like he's already heard those videos of Alex going off on me. I sent thank you them myself
Yeah, he can analyze for himself. He's pretty smart. I mean if you want to replay a video of you know
What did I say to you what was that I was very nice to you
Did you see that shit
What is my response to her
Can you
Yeah, read my respond when she fucking said shit like trying to incriminate you and take your channel down
What do I say read it? I?
Don't like midnight as a mod really
I'm talking in the chat. I'm sorry. Oh, it's gonna read it. I'll read it. I read the messages. Oh, yeah
What did I read to find this is our last messages? Yeah
Well, so there's like a bunch of video that says
As she said kind of like open to diamond said
I sucked raising so good
To me and what did I say and respond to all the videos that she sent to me
You got to take it you got to take it now now. You got
it. He said I know I had others say bad things about shit to
me too but people say you want to fly like you like we just
need to tell them to controls panel better and then you
sort of set you then you talked about raging is you see that
raging raging
What did she say? I sucked him off this and that like a weirdo. Yeah, but what is she trying to do?
She was sending me clips of you like on your channel when you were sleeping and she was like recording a shit and
Flagging you and she said and I said you can talk to psyche about it on the panel
Like let's not like why are you going after his fucking channel? Just talk to him read that what I wrote what I say to her
No, you said what I know I had other things
No, I have your back or not psyche
Yeah, you did
And thank you
And thankfully, you know
Everything was okay, but you know
I really do appreciate your look
What does your respond when I say
Like, you can talk to psyche
I didn't respond to you
I didn't respond to you. I didn't respond to you either. You literally just said I'm sucking.
I didn't respond to you. What is my grating name of this? I didn't respond to you today telling
that I suck reading stuff. Why are you messaging me? Don't message me. Why are you harassing me?
I don't give a fuck what you're doing with Dima, but I really want Psyche to see what did I say when she was trying to take your channel down?
I said you can talk to him.
I know I had other things bad shit to me too, but people say you want to play Psyche.
I said nobody needs to be trying to take, I understand where you're coming from with Alex, but you don't need to be taking this channel down.
Like this is all you said.
I know I had others say bad shit
Alright, your fat fucking fingers, your manly fingers already showed it to fucking Psyche
And I'll show more
A little bit and a little bit is coming up about your Stadia's behavior
She just utes you, she restreams you, she fucking takes over whatever you want
Like Psyche
All right, I got your back, but you know what?
You can have a dick like this fucking talking shit and then you know what?
She's harassing me.
Message me about raging demon.
I don't give a fuck what you do with raging demon.
Like, why are you messaging me about raging demon?
You're saying I sucked his ass.
I did that.
You're weird.
Like you're a weirdo.
You're a weirdo.
I would use them.
Okay, psyche.
Can you read the messages about raging demon that she's done to me now?
i sent him the three yeah no no let him read it let him read it
psyche why are you messaging me read it read it where can i find where can i find though
you just you just already saw it like it's after that after she threatened your channel
and i said leave him alone you can talk to him like what is after that what is after that what
Like
She put she put she titled the discord chat stye gone or something
Like stye is gone
What is she right?
Um, I don't think I have that part there because I don't see I don't see the graphic any other words
I just see like the video. Okay. So maybe it wasn't that important, but right what like read that's like
I'm sucking raging demons asshole right now. Like what is she sending me?
My ass he says I
Stuff's raging so good. He forgot about your drunk ass. He ate my ass. He loves what me more than anything
I'm lying, right
She's messaging me weird shit like an hour ago.
You're a same shit.
You're literally why should we people alone?
You weirdo, you're like, you can never, you can never be a radio.
All right, you go to his channel and you try to strike it.
And I tell you to fucking leave him alone.
You can talk to him and then you message me because you're a fucking weirdo.
You're a weirdo. No, you're saying you're a predator weirdo.
Leave me alone.
message me for I don't give a fuck like you're sucking his ass or not
You wouldn't ever touch you I was not on the phone reading. Thank you. Can you take her for a second? She's the app and over me
She's the app and over me do you see her she sent me videos she said like
Alex said that's to me on psyches panel. She went after your channel. And what do I say? I said you can talk to him
Don't go after his channel
I know and I don't know. Are you scared again? No, I'm not scared. I'm not scared
But I don't know she understood exactly what the flip flicked up
Anything to you or your channel
No, no, you don't okay. I would never threaten it and again
I don't give a fuck anymore
But tell this fucking bitch not to message me about weird shit like she's doing to raging demon in her fucking
Fantasies like she did with fucking Miguel and like other people like she thinks like she's with everybody else
She's delusional and you want to be delusional with her? I never went after your channel. You're scared. I would never get back to you
I'm I'm I'm I'm a fucking evidence that she's going after your channel. I don't go after I
Yeah, and it's like and I don't it's really sad in this world that somebody nice like me
Like me that doesn't go after your channel has to be dismissed and I'll leave forever
But you'll let somebody evil like that. Will you know?
Fucking weird dick ass bitch that lies about everything, right?
Well, you know, it's like from the beginning and we had to battle her fucking shit
Well, it's like
You know, I think I think she made it. It's like you you already saw her jerking off
That's okay, I jerk off to you but it's like yeah, it's the whole day
Trying to expose my fucking shit
I haven't said shit to her everything I've ever done has been nice to her
everything
Yeah
Well, I don't I don't think she outed raging demon. I'm sassy. I think that you know
It's cut more sexual. He's more complicated than that
And like you know, nobody gives a fuck about raging demon. I'm talking about you
I see I see I know but it's like I can't wait. I mean it's like
What she does like reaching demon is not in the same facility. He's in different continent and even if they were together
I would not be jealous. It's really sad that she does this to men over and over and she thinks it's funny
Oh, this guy wants me. This is her way of like going, but I don't give a fuck about that
I care about what is the reality she went after your fucking channel red flags?
Okay, I don't go after your channel
I'll leave your channel
Well, it's like I mean, I don't want anyone to leave me say I I mean, I don't even like
They're mad at Tony. I mean, it's they are really is like I'm I'm like my channel is a I
Amita I supported you. I brought a lot of people here
I've donated more than that fucking girthy diamond has ever in her fucking life
My friends have donated more than her and it will just that said I can only do enough
I don't I don't know and I don't even have to donate
I'm a fucking like content creator too that needs donations as well, but I don't even care
I care about loyalty
I care about friendship. I care about some morality. Okay. Yeah
I would never do that fucking shit to you. Okay. I mean, I think I can just I can all I can do is like
You know try to try to like prevent it, but you know, I can only do so she's right on your panel
I just send you proof that she's like literally I know. I know. Oh, I talk to her again right now
Oh, I'll find out if she would ever what is she gonna do is soften it up. Fuck her. Tell your message me
I will fucking drag that bitch and dog walker
I mean uh that whole uh skank fucking dog walking man
Shut up with your fucking ugly spandex you neon whore. You're so ugly bitch. You look like a neanderthal. Okay
Go die. Go die in little bits. Nobody cares. Uh, I actually showed you those videos
Psyche like now she's showing you shit that I've been sighting you
I sent you those three videos of how Alex booked me on the 12th of this month
It's not what, let's see, today is the night.
You both here?
And I'll be just showing you that I clipped those.
You both here where?
That I showed you already.
Oh, okay, okay.
I showed you those videos already Saiki on the 12th, it's the 19th that I'll be just showing you these videos when I've been showing you.
I know, I know, I know. I mean, it might, you know, I didn't get, like, people were thinking you struck the channel.
Like, she flagged some content and the video was put out of age restriction.
but it wasn't it wasn't I know but I know but that's that's the problem is that it's like
that's the problem it's like with a lot of people too I mean it's like so
I don't want to I don't want to like really bring it I just like I'm done with that situation
and it's like it's in the past okay so I'm not worth it's like you know you you're Alice made up
I don't care about the Alex situation like
No, I mean, I care because it's like, you know, it's kind of like, you know, it brought danger to my channel, but from both of you.
I just, on that day, she's showing you old fucking videos that I showed you on the 12th, literally the date of...
No, I know, I know she did the videos, but I didn't, I didn't, you didn't say anything about, like, when you sent those about,
hey, I'm gonna, like, you didn't even give me a warning, like, hey, if you take down the video, or can you, like, you know...
I literally told you on the 8th.
at 8.32 on six. Yeah, but I didn't, I didn't wake up in, I didn't, I didn't wake up in, I didn't wake up until I knew Alex was talking about, um, I know, but I was, but I was still, I know, but I was still asleep, I was still asleep, so I, I, I, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can, I can't, I can, I can't, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can, I can
multiple people try calling your texting you that same day
It's just before doing like that doesn't talk to me talk to me before because I can I can you yeah
Yeah, okay. Yeah, that's fine. We don't need yeah, we don't need to keep rehashing
It's kind of complicated
I showed you a long like days ago already
and she's trying to make that into like an epic game.
Put that on stage, put her backstage.
Put your mic.
Put her out of one ear.
So the 12th was like 12th, the 12th was old, right?
That was like right after it happens. You're on me. I know if I just uh fixed your microphone. Today's the 19th.
It was like the 12th is like the 12th is the 12th, right?
So yeah, it happens. So that's what I had. That's what Alice and her were on the show. It was probably like the 12th and then she wrote me like the next one.
And then why is she messaging me today and trying to like say like all this shit about like this fucking raging demon guy?
That's probably mostly not true, and we already know that. Why? Like what is wrong with her? Why is she messaging me?
I don't know. I think we need to do you see the date on look at the date and when she fucking was trying to take your channel down
She happened would you forgive me if I did that to you it happened all the next morning
Would you would you would you actually forgive me if I did that to you?
I probably would like eventually I probably would because it's like
It's like the kind of thing like people are saying like
Forgive me if I flagged you eventually
Well, I think I can't stop. I mean, I just can't like if people could have threatened that and try to scare you with that
I can't so I just have any respect for you. Do you trust me?
Well, no, but I don't know how I understand. No, you understand the flagging process and like more about it than for you
I don't think anybody is the part of of you. I don't think they give two fucks about you. Okay?
No matter how mad I get like I would never do that to you
Watch out when she flags you again
I wasn't happy and it's like yeah, it's like but then it's like if you if she if you get her mad right now
Then she's then it's like she might and it's like I have nothing to do with it
It's just because stuff between you guys so I'm just trying to say
Fucking like
That's why I need to have a talk with her, you know, but I did have a talk with her already
and it's like we kind of came to understanding that she's not going to do that in the future.
You're really serious? You think that's what's going to happen?
I forgive him. I forgive him. I forgive him for bombers. She's done the similar things.
I'm going to give my channel.
She porn bomb you. She porn bomb me. She just puts out her fucking titties to people.
Yeah, I think we were like, you know, we didn't take us down when she did that.
You know, it's like, it's not about taking it down.
It's about her doing whatever the fuck she thinks she thinks is funny for our attention.
Oh, it's like, it's not going to be funny.
And then it's like, there'll be no, you know, it's like, the platforms are gone.
And, you know, it's like, it'll be like, there's no, the content's gone.
There's this place to go.
So it's like, that's not good to like harm.
It's like good to keep the infrastructure good.
It's like, you have a problem with the host.
You know talk to the hotels, you know talking to chat you can like you people talk shit about me all day
But it's like when I kind of say like the like the other side of youtube like
Like people that people should like kind of like just mind their own business there
Like I would never flag or anybody or as just as it's not in my
Not something I would never you flag. I would never flag. I don't time out people. I don't go and like play like mod wars
I don't like exploit people for their entertainment. None of that
Enjoy a psyche and I always believe in like what goes around comes around. I believe in karma
I believe in that in like ways that um like morality and like handling things
I'm sorry that you're you know
You tolerate that, you know, I'm really sorry. I'm really sorry. Um
Well, I just
There's no excuses for that when it comes to that fucking shit. That's not a fucking friend. That's somebody
I'm using you. I've never seen you. I never restream you ever
Don't need
Well, you know, I think that you know for even if you know, it's like me man, so it's like you know
Many massive like a talented fucking he doesn't own fucking shit, okay?
He's been around way before this fucking dirt bag that you're fucking trying to defend, okay?
Can you do this like one big favor?
Change your like angels like and put a a female up there at like a butch one
That looks like a fucking big monkey with a dick in front of it and then you know instead of me. That's dirty diamond
Okay, I'll do that. Okay. Thank you
She's literally
Like I literally told her I was on the phone with Regine. She didn't believe it. So I sent her screenshot
She didn't believe it and she still thinks I'm not on the phone with him. I
Already proved I was on the phone with him to Sam man and Sam
Yeah
She's never she's never been first you've never met him first I bet and it's like and then if you know
It's like he's some guy in England. It would be getting all everyone to all you guys in fight and like and so I really yeah
Yeah, you literally just fucking she literally just went off to say oh
Then she showed me some screens out of a phone call. Yeah, cuz they're not times that I wasn't on the phone with him
She's the she's gonna brought it up again. So I'm just clarifying what she's saying
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on, bitch. This is they nobody wants. Oh
I'm sure you say hi
I mean, in her day, she literally went on here originally to just fucking say shit to me
because Barry got under her skin about raging the day prior, and then she saw me.
And that's when she started going off on me about raging, and that's why raging is even
a subject right now.
Well, it's kind of weird like, you know, it's like sometimes like when there's like relationships and then it's like
There'll be like a third party and then people will get mad at like the third party rather than their spouse
Who like went to the third party, you know, and so it's like there's even even here. I don't know
So it's like yeah, it's like you never really know exactly
You know
It went in the third party situations
I mean, it's just, all this is just becoming repetitive.
Like it's just the same thing that's been going on
for hours now.
Yeah, yeah.
You can say it's the top, it was good.
Anyone can come up and help change the topic.
We can talk about other stuff.
Yeah, it's beginning like a little bit of a,
you're just making this all for attention right now.
Cause I don't like to bring up like,
because like when something's done,
it's like, when something is finished,
it's like,
Kind of like you know file that away in history. It's like you don't have to like
It's like it's like kind of like kind of like it's just brings back bad memories and it's like, you know
It's like we all make mistakes. I think I talked with you about it. It's like I don't think you do that to me again
And it's like but I mean it's like, you know, and luckily of course it's nothing nothing that bad happened
But you know, I probably would be probably more unforgiving if something bad happened
But you know, it didn't and so, you know, I think
You know no damage, whatever it's all it's all good
I don't know, in the end I know she's about her about raging, I get that, whatever, but it's just the fact that she feels the need to say, he was more serious about me, all this shit, like, she doesn't know what we're talking about.
Yeah, I don't know how serious he really is, but anyway, I don't know, I mean, he's just, he's, you know, he's, you know, he's mad at me some days, he likes me some days, he...
You know
Like you know when he's mad like you he'll make it know when he's mad and like when he because he's an opinionated person and you know when
So he'll like, you know, he doesn't always come across right, but
You know, that's all
Like I don't want to speak on him, but you know
No, I don't know. If I have one Christmas wish, I wish everyone in the chat could all get along and exchange a super Santa gift, and, you know, let bygones be bygones, and, you know, especially on the YouTube, this YouTube world is so...
It's so like different from the real world and we're just like still kind of navigating it
It's like so different but it's like it's so much of it's so fake
But so some of it's like spills so real and I it gets really personal
I mean it's just it gets it's just like a it can be emotional loco sir. That's why I'm here
It's just the fucking internet like yeah, it's like yeah, if you don't take it too seriously you don't like you know
I can't like I you know
I
Know I get attached to people and I like people. I love people at me
Online and I want to meet people in real life too by the math majority people
I'll just I'll just you know be talking to on the phone and
You know, we'll have our own lives in this world and
My my old porn that I was paid for I don't care like I make tranny chasing content. That's all I've been doing
Like, fucking for a while now is making training, chasing content and to be like, oh, here's
a video of Flirty Diamond where she got paid a while ago, a while ago.
Nothing new.
It's like, fuck, if you're gonna show videos of me jacking off, at least show a recent
one from Twitter, like fuck.
Don't show like an old video of me jacking off, like fuck.
I'm just saying like it's just I don't care about this shit like I'm making whatever contents giving me money on different platforms like
Manning that's serious to me
Yeah, well, you mean we were talking about Sebastian Stallone his first his first movie was like I think I'll call it breaking kitty's wedding or something like that
Or like it's called it was something like it was something like low-budget soft-core porno
He got paid $125 1973 to make it
And then he, then he got signed to, well, I guess Rocky and they re-released it, you know, called the Italian Stallion, you know, so they can capitalize on it.
But yeah, I mean, a lot of people will do like little...
Things for money and if they get the entertainment industry which they're already kind of almost in if they're in the
Transcontent is fucking Jackie Knopf and some tits up on the videos because that's it
It's a fetish
Category and that's the most trans chasers want to see is some tits for Jackie Knopf and I mean fuck it
Like it is not hard to find like like a really straight guy
I'm the straight like the straight guy and then try to be like it's like, you know, like some of them are
And you know, they're not interested in the whole dick aspect
And then just fuck the girl hard and then there's tranny chasers who want the dick who want the boobs who want everything
There's just there's differences between the tranny chasers versus the guy just happened to date a fucking tranny
Yeah, I mean because it goes back to like the fetishes. I'm like, you know, there's like, you know, imagine like, you know
There's doors and there's like people like, you know different, you know
Different different physical things about them and there's people that have a sexual fetish it
And so when they see that they're not falling in love with the beautiful dwarf woman. They're
They're
They're horny and then they want to have sex with a dwarf.
I mean, I don't know.
It's like, it's so, and then it's like,
then after, if you're going to finish.
I guess it's a thought, yeah.
I mean, and this is really what's going on.
We're in Cali, we're in Cali, no one cares.
Like, this is coming from her.
You can you can you think people can marry into their fetishes, or is that like too weird with the partners?
I had an old sugar dad
He wanted to marry me but he wanted to give me a lower allowance because I would be living with him and I said fuck you
Well, that means it's like rent rent is thousands of dollars. I mean, so that would probably yeah, but my money
I don't I don't care about the material I get the materialistic shit by myself
I mean, that's I mean, I think it's just like a shelter. I mean, it's like a place you can like even if you
Yeah, that's always nice. I mean, that's a valuable it's a valuable thing. I mean, you know, I don't know
You want a little daddy? You want to you want to lower your allowance because you want to be like when I had this offer before
I just told the dude I want the same amount of money and if I'm not gonna get it
I'm not gonna live with you because I'm making more money not living with you
so
He got mad cuz he got too far into his delusion
but me I always had my mind on the prize and
That's really it like I mean
We're trying to get we're trying to get into his will or something no
Bad
No, I'm married. I just you know my for me. I was just looking at the money
He was falling into his delusions
Wanted me to live with him for a lower amount of an allowance. I said no
But yeah, there's guys that have living they live in fantasy. I mean look at that that
Frickin trans racial fucking
Um, that transracial bimbo she her man is taking freaking tan shots with her
And you know, she's living her best freaking life while her man is funding all her surgeries and her tan
So it's just you know
Well, I'm talking about like I'm talking about like the
Sexual fit. I mean for like I don't think any man like really gets off on being a daddy
I mean, it's like this because it's a necessity, you know part of the part of the
Part of the whole thing, you know, I don't think but there are you know pay pigs that will like, you know
Can they do like like to be told to like send money and then they get like this like sexual
It's really weird thing. It's like people that find find those people that get it's actually turned on this and money
That's the that's a kind of a jackpot right there. I think at least the found found a few of those
That's I mean like things come and go just fucking live life in the moment when it comes to that shit
Cuz yeah, it's hard to keep a client for that fucking long after fucking dreaming his wallet
He's gonna try to
Maybe like maybe they don't don't mean don't train the wall. It's so fast in the you know, you know
Just like, you know one less lately handbag a week or something like that and then, you know, then
It's not just you know bunch of shit, and that's just really it, but like I mean fuck it like
People like what they like and that they like who gives a fuck
Yeah, I've never I mean I think I mean I've watched trans
Transporn in this thing. I'm not like I've watched it
I've watched it and it's like and then it's like I think they always have it have the dick in them
And like but it's always like soft. They're like Harley and Harley can draw a hormone
So it hardly ever gets hard and so it's always just like flop it around
And then like, yeah, and then it's like, yeah, then uh, yeah, come on up, easy show enjoy and so, I mean
I just watched a little bit, it's like not, it's not my thing, but it's like, I do, I do like, I do kind of like
think like men that are into trans, I kind of find them attractive. It's like, you know, it's weird because they're just like kind of like
freaky, you know, I don't know, I just find them.
You just want a man that, you just want, like I said, you live off a fish taco and dick.
I was on a man. Yeah, I was on a man to be my be the lettuce of my fish taco
Hey, just talking about my uncle. Can you please like?
Remove her out of the touch. Yes
Hey, the turtle is talking about my uncle. Yeah, remove take her wrench and suck him throughout
Okay, that was like one that was like the one like the like one thing I said when I you know
Like how do you thank you?
Okay, but I didn't want to do it. I don't want to put her I can like I'm
I know I'm a managing mind. I'm just letting you know
My family I'll fuck her up
I hope it's not gone right now. Hold on.
There's my phone.
Oh.
Hi, babe. I don't know where my phone went.
Hold on.
You can go into my chat.
Hold on. Hold on a second.
Oh. Hi, Chiris.
Your shoes.
It's fucking 5.13 fucking a.m. in this shit storm
Like thank you, this has been going on I think since like 1 a.m.
Hold on
Yeah
It gets really hard when it gets really hard when it's like
Like I asked like I say, you know, just it's like, okay. Oh
I have not read that comment
Shout out to the don't know okay be my supporter
But you get you get that I think that the comment can be deleted like that that the comment can be deleted on the door
Well, you want okay? I just don't have I can't don't have my phone in my my tablet. I have to take off my
Stream yard to get my my YouTube is so
But yeah, I mean yeah, and like you know, she's just it's like you know just timed out for a day, but it's like
You know
Mm-hmm
But I agree because I told her like I was like just so I think don't I like just don't talk about
You know in general and it's like and then she has been good for like a few weeks everything was good
And then she says we got so it's like it's just
Oh god.
It's a little bit wild here.
So looks the cake show.
It smells more pot.
What time is it?
It's 5.16 a.m.
It's like 5.16 p.m. psyche.
It's not like half of you.
It's been going on for an hour.
Okay. Oh, can you get in a mod? Yeah, a mod can just click on it and say delete message
Tell me if it says I have to do it
believe that
The guests on the panel support are gay. Oh my gosh, simple is why are you so rude and like why is it like all these like it's like
Countess Bathory and Zimples who's like Vlad the Impaler, they're both like these Transylvanian
Whack-Os, the biggest mass, they're mad at me. And it's like, you know,
his historical figures are interesting, but I don't know these people, there's nuts.
I just, I don't know. It's all a lot right now, psyche. This is just a lot for her.
This is just a lot for me too. It's a lot for the morning. Yeah. Well, it's going down there's 71. So
Oh, yeah, this is psyche. This has been going on for so long. Like
I'm not even like playing like this is
I think this is 147. Oh my gosh. Oh, yeah, I mean, yeah
Yeah, I mean, I've been only I've been only up. Yeah
Yeah, but I'm just saying it's like you like we have went on a whole rant about you and I actually
She was talking about just calling pretty much calling people fake and like she went on a whole rant at once
one whatever a
Yeah, I mean I say if my crucible goes on easily bitching about that. I've timed him out five hours ago. I mean it's like you'd be like hey
What about it?
Yeah, yeah, so I say yeah, it's like really like families are off limits and it's like I really like you know families are important
You know, it's like and I you know, it's like it's just something we all
or like I say the
majority of us
Even don't get along with everybody in our family. We'd love our family and then it's like it's very personal when and it's
I just think the lowest kind of troll tactic to like bring up people's relatives even if it's indirectly it's just
Alright pk
She's just she's just just an a coma for for a short time until until she comes out of the
YouTube YouTube jail
Needed to take a break in her shell
Have some coffee back in the turtle shell come on come on
Sorry, I'll speak clearly be clearly. Oh
It's like he how are you? How are you so drinking I have not had my beatbox if I finished it like two hours ago. Oh
It's okay. Well, that's good, but that damn is too early to be drinking. I'll pace myself.
Hey, Sean.
It's five to ten minutes. She'll go like, okay, well, great. You know, it's like, you know,
but, you know, I'm happy to be here. Maybe she'll like, she's on my show and
you watch it over there. I don't know. Squidbiz has a, oh my gosh, she does.
You're oh here Kate like where you're going Kate that da-da-da
You're okay
Your YouTube jail you got your photograph, you know your book for 24 hours, and so we'll see you tomorrow
No electric chair
What what ah is how much you guys need?
How much you guys dick right?
What's all we talking about it's on I don't think what's ah, it's like what's ah
You know saying ah like what's ah is how much?
Yeah, flirty diamond. I we're kinky or I mean we need another. Oh my god
I mean, I think we need like another man in the bedroom, but you know
He's gonna be a really interesting guy, but
Move like it work. Who is it gonna be Joker Joker flirty or Alex Joker?
Okay, yeah, fuck you. Are you still fucking Joker from me taste still fucking Joe shively from me
You so raising even from beta, so I got even
I don't count. Oh
I don't know. I don't know. I deserve region you and body for test use. I'd look for the BKG test
Okay, I'm gonna get a demon tattoo
Nice
Allison's Joker. Yeah, we're gonna have it. We're gonna we're gonna move to Salt Lake City and all we're all gonna rock
I'm gonna I'll have several wives. Oh
my god
Thank you for that. It's got a catch-up donation for some future readings for the chat. And so maybe I'll do some
Maybe do some this morning, but I want to thank the donator for the catch-up that really is awesome
I really and then you took fucking
Alex for me too psyche. I think I was
Um, who else you took for me? Okay. Well, you can you can you can have Barry you can have Barry and you can have
Joe
Please keep them pages now page took Joe
but you took um, oh
Yeah, you took mr. Big Pipes for me. Oh my god. Well, I want to can I give it can I give him back?
I want to give him back. No
Yeah. So you took Mr. Big Price for me to knocking on your door. Is it knocking on your door with a accordion and a banjo and a harmonica?
Hey, I was going to chill. Hey, no, I know.
What even happened to Alex?
No, I don't know. I don't know. I think Alex is...
Of course he lurking. He has to be lurking somewhere.
Big fives go to before I go to flurry out. No, thank you. Mr. Big Pipes
Mr. Big Pipes is into I think I think there's a like there's a few guys
I've noticed a few guys are in our into it better. I think our potential take granny chasers
I think I found a few I think I see it. I think I just need their behavior
Birdo took Sam and for me
Oh, do you want to know your name would be your name would be his name would be pipes diamonds. Isn't that be cute? Oh my god
Thank you. That sounds like that sounds like I'm smoking on something
That was Maya's joke. Yeah, that just sounds like someone's moping on something
That does not sound good. I'm five diamonds. It's more valuable than pipe crystal
No, that sounds like freaking that's what's like some crackhead shit. Yeah
Yeah, no
Um
Sam man for me
Birdo did oh my god that that like that that that that yeah, I was I was having
Very insane and we're fighting for me and then Birdo hopped on panel and smoothed up Sam man
And they ran up into the sunset yelling at each other
Oh, it's a massive couple though. Birdo and Alex. I shipped them together. They both have that high volume, you know
Yeah, they can each day
Further wedding we can get the microphone
They'll never bother
I should birdo and Alex together
Then they be cute together. I think they'd be awesome
Diamond, did he, hold on, let's see, make it happen.
Diamonds, pipes that had the better ring to it, yeah.
Pipes crashed out in the Corvette, yeah.
He also damaged the RV and then tried to say
that it was the guy's fault.
Nor even this, Mr. Big Clats.
I haven't seen him in chat for a couple days.
I think he's like asleep, man.
No, what do you think I did?
I just want to chill.
You guys, there's this jelly of me.
My dick is like eight inches three-quarters long
I still bury from Kate
Actually, I'm thinking about it
I'm really clean on the man
It's so big so bear from Kate. Yeah
I wish I ever shopping cart or and I'd ever I don't know she had she had in her in her like in her
What so does what was it? What are those bags called that you that you like see you steal you like wrap up in tape inside?
And they're called like I forgot what they're called. Oh, I
So so so there's people like with there's you can take a handbag like a plain handbag
And you line the inside of it with like electrical tape and then that the the alarms won't go off
or anything in there.
It's called something bag.
I forgot.
You know when you were sort of retail,
you probably heard of it.
Kind of like a booty bag or something,
or a booty bag or like a burger bag or a booty bag
or something.
I think it's a BB.
I don't know if it's not a BBL.
Anyone heard of it?
Alex, like, Alex, Alexander, yeah.
It's not, it's not the other.
Oh my God.
Thank you, Lito.
Okay, so.
It's a back. Oh, that's it. I'm not much back. Oh, I have very little very little bit
but
Now when you say
Alex's name in the mirror three times. He'll pop up. Oh
my gosh, yeah
He's like bloody Mary, but you know
Alex
yeah, but he's bloody Mary, but the microphone is way louder and
The mirror just cracks, you know, and then he arrests you
And first year this is a first because I not him easy. He's the one that decorates the
The what decorates the sugar is super
Oh, oh, he's a super who's I'm gonna get some sleep because this fucking it's late early
Hey diamond, thanks for being on the show. Have a good night. Well, I'll see you later
Bye tell demon I said hello, okay
Call who or call. What do you give me a call?
Are you are you back there tricks? You should just check. Are you here me talking?
Call who easy who I'm confused. Oh, Alex Alex Alex come back
Interesting morning, okay. I know and I know look it's just me
Just me little me
Hey, I take the story
Sorry, I actually didn't kick up my microphone. I was saying Paige like look look I got these a little borealis life
Look they go all the way to see and I my page of a sexy story about about a friend of mine
Half the last night. There's one more of my fantasies came true. Now. What am I proudest fan fantasies?
What am I fantasies nonetheless? It was I got to see straight
I'll tell you later. Okay. So, how am I at you? Anyone hear me now? Can you hear me now? Tommy? Can you hear me?
Yeah, I have another beer to drink. It's 6.30. I'll just get a beer.
Loli.
Hi, come on.
Hi, babe. Hi.
Hi, babe. Hi, baby.
I mean hear me good, okay
Yeah, the Sun's coming up a guy that I did organize like my whole room today. I like vacuum
I hope I didn't break the vacuum cleaner. I think it kind of kind of started
Bugging out a little bit, but I can't fix it. I know every perfect leaders. I
Clean up my table. I organize all my cards. I already take all the books all the clothes or everything is a separate and piled
It looks so good
So but I want to I want to wait till I get the whole house done to do the house tour
But I'll do it probably and I think it'll probably be like a
Week I think I can probably get it done this week. I'll try
Give me give me the give me the end of the give me to the end of the month
Me ten days
It was perfect. Okay, I
Surex, you like the colors
The magic cat six is all
I wish I would have had this along with the DMC last night. Oh, yeah
That was good it was it was actually so good that I mean I could have asked like oh can I get one more time before they left
I was I was like I had it. I always say it was so strong. I was like there's no trip
I'd be better than that
Because I think I'm as strong as trip I ever had
Crazy drug what miss it's a drug, but it's like
It's a pretty innocuous one doesn't really have any physical
Downsized to it. Maybe let's see you're not mentally prepared for it, but
Hi, you're sitting by the you're sitting by the candle your pink cat
Hi
Have a kiss I can have one kiss can I have one kiss?
Mm-hmm
Katie's mad way
Oh, no, am I am I probably featured on the show? Oh, I don't know my my phone went though
I put it down somewhere, but I can't I don't know where
You only be so many places
Hey, babe, it's okay. It's okay. Oh, here's
Yeah
Good morning good morning tricks
Let's drink some water and do morning sketches the stretches, okay
Stretches we can use me I like to do yoga I say like who's really the yoga in the past
Let's see what miss which I just want to see what she's doing like I mean what she's came to stream something after me or something
Oh no, oh my god
Hey, please do not stop it
Not cool. That's not cool. What food? Oh, she wish you ordered for food. Hmm. I
Like a I always like a good bagel in the morning a good bagel of sometimes if you like one of those like you know
Egg egg sandwich not a McMuffin, but you know any kind of egg sandwich or I think McDonald's sandwiches to hash brown
I don't know. I love breakfast food to like norms
like norms or like
Denny's and
Hi, babe cats going crazy. It's light. He's you feel like that weird
This yeah, ah
Yeah wine for breakfast. Yeah, I'm having I'm probably having I think I have I don't know if I'll drink it
I think I think that's I think I was fine with my drink. I'm not gonna get like drunk this morning, so
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't shoot my cord. That's my last cord. You shoot all my other cords. Please don't shoot that one. No.
It shows you're on the cord. As soon as I...
Turn my head is gonna go for it. He's looking away. He's pretending. He doesn't let's see it
He's just looking away. He's just looking at the wall as soon as I turn my head. He's gonna church. Oh, you know
He's already looking at he's okay. He's yeah, he's already looking at I know your game. I know your game tricks
I'm moving the cord away from you here
I'm not biting my cord
First of all, it's very unhealthy the cat
Think I'm saying good go to go to Grubhub or
Door-dash and like look for like the little specialcy breakfast and they all they serve is like a certain breakfast
Go for one of those those are good. If you ever for order it. Well, this is gonna Dunkin Donuts get a donut
coffee
little you know a little maybe a
Smuff I don't know like it's like something like a little bit
Dinner food you want dinner food?
Starbucks, they served dinner all day.
Oh yeah, so Paige, this is on Tmoo,
this is on Tmoo, look, look how beautiful,
it was on Tmoo for six dollars.
What's the shipping included?
And it came in like four days,
like I was like, oh, the Tmoo, there's no way,
there's a good deal.
But yeah, I was like, I just ordered,
that's all I ordered, it was like six dollars, 50 cents.
And it got here like five or six days from China.
It's like it's like, you know, it's like it was like really it's like not like the most like you know
It's not like oh my highest quality thing. It's like but it's like it works perfect
I mean it has the effect is perfect. Not everything needs to be like oh
Yeah, and beaded. Yeah, if you want to come up for a reading or anybody else, you know
I'm gonna come up for a reading of fire to a fireman or easy camera. I don't know if you just sit here
I know
stuff going on
But I love you be done. You know, we'll work things out. No, yes, we are you know, I
Only have love for you, okay
So I don't have a page to the come by 7 a.m. I got it. I'm probably gonna go
I've been smoking this unicorn party the unicorn party is like they're they're like, you know
they're rounding up the unicorns right now ready to
Have them dehorned so I need to
Let me to you know escape the party before that happens. So
That's 7 a.m. I
My electric bike turns into a pumpkin and some rats
There's actually really cool there's a really cool psychic I watched today, which is a terror reader, right?
If she has like this placemat, I don't know where she had this placemat. She either got it like really expensive like through like some like
4020 like you know new age shop or she got it for at the dollar store, but it basically is just like it's a house
It's like it's like this house and
So and so she like splits it up into all the sections of the house
And then she like read for the different sections. This is what's in your basement
These are the bodies very the basement the skeleton the attic
This is like what the chimney means. This is like what's coming out of this bedroom
This bedroom is in the guest room and so it's kind of like this like a metaphor for the world
It was a really interesting reading but there were there were in my attic there were rats in my attic or mice
There's mice. There's there's and they're they're very well-dressed mice. They're like a little cute mice couple. It's almost a shame
That I have to keep them out of my attic, but they're
Very nice mice couple
You're thinking you need a reading too feeling a little bit low and emotionally mentally physically drain
Okay page will be page, you know anonymous donator
Send in for some readings and so
You'd like you could have that one of those more detailed readings
I think I'll do three like three of the five dollar readings for the chat throughout the day
Yeah, it's like and it's like, you know, it was just it's just like I mean I had that I had that
There's like light thing and it's like then my friend last night that guy told you about he like said oh
He's like can I put that in the bedroom? I was okay
And it's like a long like long tight pull and you just put it behind the bed and it kind of lights up behind the bed
It's not like pretty good
And so then I just plug this one in and it's like it's a lot better like see it's like how pretty it is
It's like really and it also you can put all these different colors. I don't know where's my
I have like a remote somewhere. I don't see it. Oh, here's
You can have like it red
Yeah, it makes the front like red you can have it and oh you can like that one
But in the fact you go home stop up linking good
Yeah, like red green
blue
Like an orange is green a purple and a blue
Dark or that's like just kind of a more purple. That's more of a light blue. It was cool streaming lady
Yeah, team use these dollars guys, you know, it's like not every you can shop like a millionaire and team okay?
I have another like I never know lamp
That's like a kind of fancy lamp and it puts like a little like stars over this like little dots
Doesn't look as good as that and it was probably $50, right?
Do you want to hear me sing a song?
This is a easy song that makes sense to you sometimes.
You guys will probably roll your eyes when you hear it.
Hold on.
You have to guess what song it's called.
Here we see it someone say yes, okay? Yeah, they are
Okay, I
Feel like I've been locked up
They stole my soul in a way. I couldn't have thought up a part of my heart was left
I thought that I deserve this punishment
Won't you punish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable
Nothing was negotiable with me. I tried to fight and pull on over on their hand to fed me
But what they did see is that I am still hungry
Baby doll, I am still hungry
I'm gonna take a taxi into the dark side of the city
Don't tell your mommy your poppy will meet me
I'm the corner with the money. Did you know that he was lonely?
You've got me feeling beat up. I'm about to turn the heat up. Bring it up to deluxe.
Asking me to give you a chance. All I want was little romance. Do you understand?
I'm going to take a taxi into the dark side of the city.
Don't tell your mama or papa you will meet me.
I'm the corner with the money.
Did you know that he was lonely?
You say you want to hold me you won't let go you said you told me I'm so beautiful
But I know you didn't say you wanted me, but I didn't notice you didn't say you didn't need me
I you didn't focus you promised me a lot you gave me less you weren't my mind neither my sex
You said you're always had my back, but now I know what to expect
Well, that out. It's Lisa Jorda club dark side of the city
That's a great song
Yeah, this will last a while. It's only 650 anyway, so it's like if the cat already destroyed the cord the cord was kind of a cheap
cheap cord but
Let's plug in another one
Pretty cool
Let's see if I can find the other one. Maybe I'll bring that out. So I have a lot of other cool stuff to bring out
there's many crystals and like
perogex and
Books and it's our and I have so much to share like I just been doing it very slowly because I want to like
Have like the audience here before I start sharing everything
Guys not one person nobody said anything about my the song I sang nobody liked it. I know I kind of messed up a little bit
Page can't stop for every little pebble on the road only boulders or mountains can step on our path. We still find a way. Yeah
But you know what a little pebble if that gets that that bitch gets in your shoe
That's gonna be what's worse than a boulder. He's gonna fucking climb over the bull the little pebble in your pebble in your shoe
That that that is the it can be painful. He's a desk down right is every like step is like a
horrible, right I
Know Lisa invited me to go out down and hang out with her
She did and or she said I can you know I can get down there get a hotel room
Can go stream with her so I just want it's gonna be it's got a little bit expensive. I you know, it's it's Florida
I'm in Los Angeles, so
Maybe I'll do some fundraising because probably just be a thousand bucks. That'd be so much fun though
And I know the chat would love it
And I would love it. She she's just like a she's a doll. She's an absolute doll
I haven't talked to her for a little bit she's on I said I'm like I'm busy with my show, but she really did
You know, I've had like a lot of angels
I think I think but at least as an honor it's like he's the angel, you know, be a page if you do a lecture and
so many others
But at least that did let me
When I was just getting started like hardly even just doing my open panels. She let me post my show on her discord
And she said I could post but whenever I wanted to I don't post anymore because I don't
her chat turned against me, but
She doesn't let anybody else be like I've never seen her do what except for like she had this
producer or friend or producer and then she they kind of turn on her and so
She she's not her discord anymore, but
Um, she lets you see she lets and she's always been kind to me. So
He gets a bad bad bad rapid publicity like the violet color over to my side of the face. Yeah
Pretty bright there. I mean, I can like learn how to point. I get my point. I can put easy back
He's just got a hold on D
I
Here here we go
This has taken back up. So do you woke up?
What is that you okay good?
I
Don't know. I hope I hope it was I
didn't think
Yeah, I'm your your your amateurs as I have like no no life no love left
But I thought it said I love feet when I looked at it
I'll change it a mother mother files from Harris Browns and make some oh
You're a brand-new owner. Oh, you're portraying it. Yeah, I love poached eggs.
Yeah, but the poached eggs are on the ground.
I don't know what type of... I'll pick it up a little bit or some shit, but it's got it.
Believe it or not, I still have a piece of...
I have my fish tacos and my corn still left over that I can heat up in a little bit.
Hey, you should warm it up. You should warm it up because you said you're going to eat it, but you never eat it.
I will.
But I just like one beer and so I just like I might make my I might show my whole
The speed of the speed of the speed was dry in the shower. It's dried off in the shower
Like a white bright white by like Kobe. Yeah, I think it's you
But I can make it different colors though. I don't know if I yeah here
We're gonna leave you guys like the best like to tell me there's like there's like the
Light blue. There's the violet. There's an orange. There's a dark blue. There's a green and there's a red
And then it does a little different effects to I think
Since they start flashing and there you go. Yeah, like that flash. Oh, it goes really fast. I
Love how fast it was
Okay, so it's a little freer than that. Okay. I like them. We have reddish violet. Yeah, the reddish violet
So here's red right here, but I'll put it back. I like that. You like to buy it on
If they think about it how cool it is though we can get like full like electronic
We're sitting next to me. Hey, you just a puppy
He's been doing good. Yeah, I'm feeling like I'm like pulling out of like
This like dark place because it's like I was just like I don't know why I couldn't like
Couldn't like I wasn't I wasn't like taking care of myself
I wasn't organizing or anything and it's like and then it but it's like but I didn't let it get too bad and I
Would dig do a little bit at a time, but it's just like it got so it was getting so much and it's like
So I just want to be able to always have a nice environment
and always be able to organize and have everything right.
This is a proper streamer.
I'm a proper streamer.
Yeah, all I think is this light.
The light and the good headphones and the good camera.
Yeah, I'm kind of getting that.
I also got a new cell phone.
I have data on it, actually.
Um
The things are going to do they're going pretty good pretty good pretty good
So it's almost over. Yeah, I don't know what's gonna happen today. So it's Thursday
June 19th, so guys it's called Juneteenth. I don't know if you've heard of that holiday
Yeah, Juneteenth today. Paige shout out to you Paige. Paige get up here Paige. Paige. Um psyche
She said she needed a reader. She's feeling down. She needs to read it. She needed to come up here
If you want to give her a reading while she stays in the chat, give her a reading in the chat. She needs to read it
Think she left
Comment at least we could give you a reading for you to see what happens so you say you need a reading you from down
You know we support your girl. So let's go
Yeah
So I'll do
Psychiatrist you can't stop for every pebble on the road only boulders and mountains can stop our path
But we still find the way around that, right?
Did you hear what I said? Yeah, but a pebble in your shoe is still very annoying and
You know, it's like it feels almost like you know almost like a boulders preferable to a pebble in your shoe
Like, you know, it's like a little pebbles too can just be the irritating and so yeah, so annoying. It's so annoying
Yes, and those are the little pebbles is after her right now
So she's gotta get rid of those and focus and focus on your goals because you're a strong woman
I could tell so on the down. They need a brown girl
And page if it doesn't work if it doesn't work out. Well, let's take your name to pebble page
With that with enormous boulders
Okay, that was better, okay
It was just a boob joke, but I know she doesn't really make sense because she okay never never might never
Hold on one second. He's just trying to make a drill. I got it. I know I know I sometimes my jokes won't land
I'm sorry. Oh
God, but you know I
Am pretty silly. Let me see. Oh, here's my lighter. Okay
But yeah, like, they're really truly funny people like, you know, there's like, you know, I can think of like, two great examples would be Jim Carrey and Robin Williams, who are just like, you know, just so beloved.
hysterical comic actors and and physical actors and yet you can tell like
there's this this deep sadness when you hear their their you know their personal
interviews like in the movies they're so funny and then they do like a
interview and they're just kind of a little bit off. You're going to tell that they've been to probably a lot of trauma and difficult times and
That's probably why they have that sense of humor. It's because it's like a it's a way to diffuse all this
negativity and tension around them and so that's why I do love the sense I live with comedy and
stand-up comics and senses of humor and funny things you know because I think that is like laughter is the best medicine and also
You can relate through humor and we can also laugh at our tragedy. You're showing a
in a purple violet rain
According to princess on
Violet rain you can do a flowering for princess violet. I see you see you see it. I
Forgot, I don't know the lyrics. I just know yeah, but it's called violet rain, right?
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Yeah. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn on the lights. Turn
Yeah, it turned out for what? Yeah, exactly. Yeah, I was just like it was blowing through the fucking
Floors of the building like it. They could take they could go to the window
To the wall to the sweat job down second balls. Oh
My gosh
What are you talking about?
Her she had a whole diamond mine grew and she saw me. She's my one choose psyche. That's what she calls another job up here
They don't want raging she really want like it. I
Brought a name. I'm not her type. I
mean, I think she's into like what I she's an amazing to my type which is like
You know
Mexican dogs, but also also like, you know
You like Mexican dogs or you don't I do and I'm and I
Find a Mexican homo dog is even more right like on the low
Yeah, I don't really like the whole but that's like yeah the homo dogs. Yeah, of course music that's interesting with me
If they call themselves the homo thug, they're probably like not like my type
I don't know they have to be like they're so straight that you would never guess right one person's chatting
It's almost like you at the gtocs never learn to god damn stupid to
God damn. We okay. Well. Thank you for the feedback that no one asked for sunshine
You brought no sunshine into the room today
Do you think Sun, is it someone named Sunshine would have like a more positive thing to say that, you know
They're I can't post their their their comments are just so obscene I would never share them
Okay, well they said they said one person chatting is almost like you f-a-g-g-o-c-s never learned
To
Goddaman stupid to Goddaman we're weak. Okay, that's what that's what sunshine their name is sunshine
And Eric isn't one be my weekend lover well Eric come on we get to where the psyche awakens terror
We all have to sleep with each other. It's a good thing. Oh, it's like a
We need a terrarium
Thanks. Oh, we need some positive energy. Thank you blows. Thank you ready cycle
You want it you want a reading or I want to let's give a panel read it
Let's see if we'll have it still here. Let's give a panel read it, but whoever just for me
Okay
Okay, I'll do a five card panel reading, okay
I'm sure I'll do it the Alice deck because the villain's deck Prince is like a little bit small for me to see this early in the morning
So, okay
But this will be like a nice little fall down the rabbit hole. I'm so okay. So this is for everybody
Spare me a resonate with you, but take what resonates and like, you know, just think about it and
Hopefully it can like give you some suggestion about how to proceed forward, you know, but look at the first few cards
it's kind of like the
The the past energies and the current energies and like the last two will be more of
Insight into the possible future, but we always we always create our own future. So never feel
Never feel like
Your phone died page. Okay page. Well, if you want to I'm doing a general reading and then you can come up here
If you want you want to read page. I'm doing five cards for the chat. Yes. There you go. I was waiting for that
Let's go bring that bring that positive. I'm cooking right now. So I'm gonna stay mute guys. Okay
Okay, so we start with the ten of ten of ten of cups. Okay, so this is like, you know, this is like this happy
family happy environment like and so it's like I think a lot of us have a
It's not grown up in it and a lot of us have created this for ourselves
It's as it says hooray the ten of cubs represents
stability comfort and happiness within your family friendships and other close relationships
Enjoy the company of those closest to you because those supportive
Connections are the most rewarding and personally fulfilling
Okay, so always remember where you came from and remember to remember like, you know the poor the love back there too, right?
Okay
Okay, where we got next for you from the Alice deck. Okay, we have okay. We have this five of flowers
So I think this is the five of one. Oh, this is the same
five or X this is
Five okay, so the five
Five of flowers. I'm thinking of the five of wands the flowers. I think are the walls. Let me check
Okay. Fireflowers. Fireflowers is usually a healthy competition. It's like a
friendly competition, but it's like it's still like a competition. Everyone's like
hitting each other with six. Okay. Okay, but no, but oh, so it's what, yeah, so it is
flowers and so it's gonna be the wads. Okay, so it's the fireflowers says
It says, five of flowers represents conflicts and competition.
You may feel as though others aren't appreciating your contribution or ideas, and this is causing
resentment.
Openly communicate your perspective and feelings in order to clear the air and restore balance
Yeah, and so don't go through all these all the time here. This is like a really like this is like a lot of my panel
Just a lot of conflicts compromises and clearing the air and talking things out sometimes
But yeah, there's gonna be when you're dealing with different personalities. You're gonna have you're gonna have
Arguments conflict personality clashes, right?
What we got next? Oh guys look what we have. Okay
We're this judgment card. So the white rabbit
It's blowing the horn
So just isn't be called, you know, this happens right before the trial
Alice has put on trial
But it just was called first. It's that it's like, you know, it gets to like
The karmic will get to the karma will get to a certain point and there's a judgment we call and then karma will be served
You know, it's it or else it would just be too much karma at once. So this is number 20 in the deck
I'll read it it says
When the white rabbit blows his trumpet
What is that? What is that? Is that your body?
Just him. Oh, it's him. I thought you were showing me your dick
Well, the right rabbit blows his trumpet to announce the rival the queen of hearts
the tarot card judgment announces the arrival of an important realization.
Judgments mark the time to make the search for past blunders or wrong doings and forgive yourself,
make amends for them, okay? It says, everyone makes mistakes. That's the simple
nature of it. Didn't I just say that earlier? Everyone makes mistakes, right?
It says whether you've hurt someone's feelings, made a poor judgment call, or
found yourself late for a very important date, judgment encourages you to make
amends and forgive yourself. You've come so far along your journey and grown so
much along the way. It's time to leave regrets and guilt in the past and move
You know that sounds like today's panel. That's crazy. That really sounds like today's panel. And while it says that, you know, people release a lot of anger today and you know, got it off the system.
That's one.
Yeah.
And now it's safe to move on.
Yeah, that's perfect for, I think,
I think, I think, because I think we're like the 10 of cups is like we come from,
it basically says we come from like some good,
like loving environments.
And that's like, I'm sorry if anyone hasn't been in a loving environment,
but I think the majority.
Are hey, what's up? It's up the loser. I think the majority of us even if they do matter how rich report
We had some harmony in our in our family and we true affection for a family
It's a happy like happy family life. I know and I'm you're not everybody, but
Even if even if not, I think your heart still came out good. Okay, and it's not I mean everybody's right everybody's
There you go
You're with him and poach eggs
Delicious looks very good
Yeah, and so then like the five of ones, you know that just that says after all the happiness like you're able to like
You know kind of have good sportsmanship when you're dealing with
Dealing with some of these situations and it's kind of like a friendly competition
But it goes too far sometimes and it's you know, it gets like it's negative
And then with that the judgment being called is like, okay, but I got since such a negative point
The hormones blown through the belt the bell is what or something. It's like and then it's like
Things are gonna be looked at and made fair, okay
Okay, so I have a couple more cards for you. Okay, so guys, I haven't pulled this one before this is oh, this is the temperance
So this is like so I think these cards are saying these last few are gonna be kind of like how to move forward the best way
And it's like this is like this is like a temperature like an equilibrium
It's like, you know temperate. It's like alchemy in a lot of ways, but it's like a potion is created
There's like, you know stars there's flowers. There's like the water. There's the moon is involved and so it's like saying, you know
have a more temperance means be temperate so it's like not too much of
anything at one time be able to mix different things together and I also on
the traditional card there is one put on the earth one put in the water well
midnight you know if I do allow it on chat you know it's like you know
It's it's it's it's the eventually like it'll come to the surface and you know
It'll be taking care of sometimes things needs to be brought
allowed allowed to
Exist to see what happens. Okay, and finally guys. Oh my gosh guys. I love this for you guys, okay?
Everyone in the pan you got the fool car. This is Alice and Alice is the fool
You know, it's like you're like, oh the fool fool the negative thing
Okay, but Alice is the fool and look she's going just starting her journey
She just sees she seems like a little white rabbit and she just wakes up from her sleep
And then she goes start chasing after it. She goes on the memory. She falls in the rabbit hole
But find an incredible journey. It's like, you know transformative in all these ways. It's like we do, okay?
but it's like we have to
You're kind of like rub the sleep out of our eyes, and take a leap of faith, but I'll read the fool car for you
I think it's probably gonna be a nicely written car and says
The fool represents someone who like Alice is about to follow their curiosity through life-changing journey
with wide-eyed yearning for adventure and a little naive,
the fool eagerly stumbles or tumbles down the rabbit hole
without much worry about where she'll end up
or what kind of tops and turbies situations.
She may encounter along the way that feels like me doing my show, right? I think I'm just like, oh, it's gonna go great today
And it's like everything goes down. Okay, right?
Okay, it says it says it says you're up to take the first steps on the adventure of a lifetime
Who knows what fantastical characters or confounding situations you may encounter
Maintain optimism throughout the journey as challenges will teach you important lessons
And as triumphs will open your eyes to a whole new world, wonderful perspective in life. Okay?
Not very clear full
I like that I like that I like that reading for everybody because I think that is like such a
And so, you know, it's a general reading, but I think like a lot of us can really relate to a lot of what was said there
And it's like but it's also like the the fool cards
It's just as you know, I'd say that's the advice for the future is to like, you know keep your
Keep one foot on the on the on the land one foot on the water or in the spirit and then
and
Have your keep your mind balanced and go with like a kind of child like
a beginner's mind. Just be curious and just have fun, right? It's an adventure. That's
what adventures are. We don't know every detail of it. It's an unexpected thing along the way
that they make it interesting, okay? So, just some PTSD. Okay, yeah, how's everyone doing?
I'm sorry, I might have missed some comments in the chat. I'll pull an animal car for the chat too.
Was good bonus pretty sure how about that
Animal and a villain. Okay. I'll pull a villain's here
The animal card you got it's the eagle. I got the eagle earlier today, you know
And our page loves these eagles and she has eagle feathers. Okay, I know I got the hawk earlier
So this is the eagle it says symbolism says power creation illumination and exploration
Almost every culture has a contact with eagles, has imbred them with power and fulfillment.
The bird is a great spirit, the creator of all things.
Eagle legends frequently involve journeys to dangerous or unknown territory, a North
East Native American myth tells of an eagle setting out with the coyote to the land of
the dead to retrieve the spirits of the deceased.
Healers venturing into the netherworld and they're given as rewards for individuals
Who show such faith as as the courage of beauty? Okay that right page? I know page is really the eagle
That's beautiful. You know, it's like, you know America
you know America's the
Bird is the bald eagle, but originally Ben Franklin suggested it be the be the
the turkey
So that'd be kind of a different kind of kind of okay. Hold on. So doing local food reviews and local spots
Think about it more like foodies. Yeah, I could do like I could do I could do I
Could you also do my like Amazon unbox things and so I could do like if I got Amazon stuff
I could do I could send people over to the other channel and I could do maybe I can do like
The bar my bar stuff there
Tell your oh, I don't know if you do want to tell that story of
Flokey, I don't know but you know easy will have to tell you psyche DEA sister. Yeah. Yeah, that is a good idea
I like it idea
I'm not 100% sure and
Andy here is mentally ill because he's agreed with
Okay, I don't want to measure him. Okay. I don't want to talk about it. Stop asking about it. Please. Thank you. Yeah
Yeah
Oh my god, I sure was so good. Thank you. I just took the last bite. Yeah
I'm saying yeah, I am in yeah, I like that. I like that idea loser. Let me see that loser
So yeah, I like that idea and there are like a lot of great
Restaurants around here and also also, I really don't get out that many restaurants because they're kind of expensive
Like I was what I went the other day to like
This really good restaurant called King Cays, which is really really good and they had they said oh, we have like a three as special like a special
Um three course dinner and I was like, I think I will probably be like 30 bucks or something at the most
It was $50 for like like a little flaming yawn a dessert and like a salad or like a little clam chowder or something
And that's not even including a drink. I mean, I was like, oh my god, so it's expensive
I mean, you know, it's probably don't get me good because meals is good, but they also give us more portions
So I understand what you're talking about. Yeah
But oh easy you would have liked it on my birthday. I went to a restaurant like my mom took me into this restaurant
And my sister used to be a waitress my sister knows all these like things about these restaurants
Like she was just new like so she found out about this at this restaurant when you show your
Driver's license if it is your birthday that day
They will give you a free steak and lobster and so and they just write it off the menu. They'd write it off the bill
And so I had a free lobster tail and in a steak is like one of the nicest like, you know
Yeah, it's like it's an I think it's $55. It's like a $50 or something like that. I'm right off on the bill
Like 50 something dollars for one just once I'm lobster tail sometimes. Yep
And it had a nice like little play on it. So you think lobster. It was delicious. Yeah, and Bruce here
Hey, you guys are really we're just taking over the camera. Hey, you're there. We
Be right back. I can let me go wash up. I got washed my head you
Okay
Yeah, these eight. Oh, it's already eight. So maybe I will drink the last of you
I don't know. I still haven't been there since this one's I'm very much a back out and I don't really like to
Have you have the what do you say?
Are you talking about me something you're calling me that and what are you calling me name? What is content?
Here's what content is content is something people watch
that they
Have give some value out of or at least like our
Entertain by a little bit. I mean it's like sometimes it's like a content is some content is good
What is content? All it is, is what I'm doing, providing you right now, you're sitting here watching my show because there's something on my show that you can't find anywhere else, right?
So, I mean, maybe you'll get assaulted and leave when I say that, but how about you create some content? You show me your content, okay?
I've created literally thousands of hours of content, okay?
What I call a content you consider
FGGO to SHIC. Okay. Well, you're entitled to your opinion, but you know, I think your opinion is
I think your opinion is just what you call me. Okay, that's what I think of your opinion
What I missed something about opinion whose opinion matters
No, yeah, but it's like something sunshine was saying. Oh my god, like, you know, you ask is f a g g o t
Like what do you think it's content is I said I think content is anything anything that people watch that keeps the entertaining
Is it's anything that uh, you know, at least keep some entertained or their eyes open or they can listen to you
It's content
Your pictures are hard and you still in you and you'd like you don't like you don't like
You know, like F A G G. Oh Jesus. No, they don't know why is you know, this is not your content
It's called a swipe and there's a swipe up and then there's another calm thing called the back button. Yeah, I
Mean because the guys it's like I was like, I know not everybody's gonna like
Me or me or my shit. I was like, you know, I'm like there's eight billion people in the world, but I'd say like
I'm not even saying the majority are in a life. I'm not even saying like 10% were like me
But I'm staying in this world out of that two billion people on YouTube
There's probably like I probably a hundred million people out of those maybe it maybe 200 million maybe five or a minute
I don't know but maybe there's at least that many that are would really be interested in my show and we enjoy it
Keep that mindset and it's like you'll keep attracting people like my my numbers keep growing
I think you're like a hundred dollar hundred viewers a week
And so, I mean, it's even if it's slow, that's what they'll build up in time. That's like four hundred a month. So it's well
That's like like five thousand a year. And so even if it is
Great in my eyes you doing great
Yeah
That's
Consistent hate of poem bombs
Assistant so that means you doing great, but I don't know poem bombing. Maybe they drag it. I keep it. All right
Uh, yeah, you don't have to watch it. You don't have to say you don't have to you can just say you can actually just block my chat
And I can that's actually blocked you and then you don't have to worry about you never have to like comment in the chat again
You can just sit here and mope in the corner
You keep you up. He wants you hateful. You keep your hateful opinions in your mind
Not because it's like they just like even like to loser sometimes is like the loser or I think the name is losers zero in the chat
And sometimes they they are dirtful, but then you see that their comment
They said hey, I have a good idea like you know
How would you go in your neighborhood and get you review on your other channels?
You have a backup channel you like keep get that one active by reviewing local
restaurants
The permit to see well depending how
That's what I'm still, I didn't look it up yet.
Gotta look it up.
Yeah.
I don't know how long those promise lies.
I want to know how long those promise lies.
If it's a month, then yeah, you could do tarot readings,
whatever price you want to put,
and then by the end, by the end of the month,
you could pay for that extra fee for the next month.
Let me continue it all.
I don't know you talking about since I'm at the steak, but you can buy a steak at the dollars and actually the dollars for them
It's a huge thing. I thought I just wanted to buy a steak right now, but I said I want to spend that money that much money
I just let me cook something
It's actually
This is so smart and so much but it's much cheaper to cook things and that's and it's like it's better to just get take out like when you're like
You know like I order in it's like cuz it's like when you're fucked up when you're fucked up or outside like real far from home
That is good. You know, I mean, yeah, yeah, and that's me quite a bit. It's like I like I love to get at night
I got like I were alcohol and then I was able to order
or
What's it called?
Norms, I was able to learn norms like a breakfast with a good steak and I was like a coffee at like three in the morning. It was so good
Yeah
How's the steak use I didn't try yeah, I'm about to bite into right now
And then you end up saving it if you bit in what today say yeah
I think I ate all the a1 off of it and then
You bit it once and you was just there chewing with a happy face and then it was over
Yeah, but I didn't I did all the potatoes and I ate all the everything else
So yeah, you would take you was digging in on the potatoes. They know it's just the potatoes. Stay good
I used to watch I still watch to this day, I still watch mad food stuff
Like on YouTube up psyche froze
There you go. Sorry. Yeah, but my phone. Oh, it just kicks me off sometimes. Here we go. Thanks.
It looked like he had the fattest blood on the block. It hurt.
Well, my, my vape is still going. Let me see how much I have. Look.
The 21st is in two days. So I said, I suggest I see you might, um, buy some weed and, you know, hit that bomb.
Yeah, and it's like it's gonna be like a little bit
You're gonna see the difference you're gonna see if your tolerance went up or your tolerance is the same
On the 21st, I probably will order
the flower yeah, or some flower and
I call it bud. I call it bud. But some bud. Yeah
You know flower or weed or
I'm going to call it. I'm going to call it.
I don't know macy's the fan. How's the macy's the face? Well, I know if you go to macy's or like north or certain like
Or department stores you get to the right area of them or if you're wealthy, you know, it's a just they see you down
They who's who's who's who said who said they could think about three hundred dollars. Oh, you fancy, huh?
Got your nails done hair done. Everything did fancy, huh?
You watch Howard Stern easy. Are you watched it? No, I used to watch it
Yeah, but I'm gonna say you know Robin is
You don't know Robin Quivers is
Okay, you really doesn't know okay, I probably tune in here and there but that's about it. Well, she's like she's like
They're co-hosts. She's like the black lady. I don't remember
Wow
Burn up now. That's why I had to eat. I had so but it's over. I was drunk all night
Oh, shit. I ain't lying. Let's show my pipe. Okay. Hold on. Don't get burned now. I say you get burnt three times
Don't go outside. No
Well, okay. Oh, that's a good question. Is there any like um superstitions you believe in?
Like not really I like I like to believe in like the opposites of the superstitions like I like black cats
I believe are just like our great luck and like I believe
You can like, you know, I go walk on the ladder. You're not gonna get bad luck break a mirror
Oh, I would be afraid man. It's like, you know, break it because it's like we do we will break light
We'll break mirrors. We'll walk on our ladders will cross black hat will cross our paths
We're like, you know, we'll whistle in a graveyard or something that there is like, you know
Weird things, but I say like it's our own mindset that kind of like
the
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don
It's the same place as the sunshine. I mean it's like you're ridiculous
I can't even I want to reference who said breaking a mirror is bad luck some random f a g g o t
You cannot even name. Well, I don't I know it's probably it's called an old wives tale. It actually
Olds tell old old women old women used to be called baggots in a in there
You know a nanny says don't break. She got tired of don't break mirrors
Don't break mirrors. You're gonna get bad luck and then evidence then
you know the kids like oh don't pick them ever gonna get some bad luck
Yeah, we don't know who made that model like it's just the same
Yeah, they just don't want them to break the mirrors and so they were like it's bad
Look if you break it and so it's here the riffraff from throwing throwing rocks at the mirrors or touching it and so
Right. It's kind of because some of them kind of were oh, then they turn into common sense, right? Okay, then they turn
Okay, that makes sense. You want to hit that you want to hike the Appalachia? Yeah
Yeah, I want to get to I want to whistle it now. Now. It's like you made me
I don't play with ghosts and none of that, but I want to see what happens
Well, I'll tell you what it's I'll say the I'll say some of that now when I leave when I leave this live
I'm gonna look up videos for that. Okay
Well, I mean, I'll just look at the, I just want to look at the whistling one, let me see, I'll see, I'll look at the whistling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, look up, look up, look up what they say about whistling there, one here, oh lord.
Let's see what they said. All right. It said in Appalachia, whistling can be both a practical matter and a source of folklore and superstition,
particularly in the context of outdoors and nighttime. Well, some view it as harmless, others associated with attracting unwanted attention from spirits or animals,
especially during specific times or certain situations.
So it says, here's the breakdown.
It says practical considerations.
It says hunting.
In the Appalachian region, whistling
can scare away game animals, like snipe, a type of rodent,
which is not even a real rodent, I don't think,
which are hunted by some locals.
Snipe hunts are like wild goose chases that don't exist.
This can lead to negative reactions
from hunters who rely on the animals for food or sport.
So, a chat TPC believes in the snipe, guys.
That's minus one for chat TPC.
So, communication with sling can be used for simple communication,
like signaling to someone or directing animals.
Here's a superstition that says...
There's a widespread belief in Appalachia that whistling at night is unlucky or even
dangerous, potentially summoning spirits or other supernatural entities.
Then it says the Seven Whistlers.
Some Appalachian lore includes the Seven Whistlers, a group of birds or spirits that are said
to whistle before the death or disaster.
Other traditions.
Some Native American traditions like that of the Kikapu tribe used whistled speech for
It's real sexy. Easy and out of flirting, okay? Okay, then it has a modern interpretation
Some TikTok videos and other online content play on the appellation folklore of whistling at night
Creating air of mystery or suspense the idiom whistling in the dark
Refers to trying to appear brave or optimistic in a difficult situation. There you go
Don't go with some crazy at night time when we're the witcher now what 3 o'clock 2 o'clock
Yeah, I'm 3 a.m. But I don't think you'd be walking around the Appalachian that I think I think maybe sunset is maybe the time to get out of there
But what about the camping there?
No, I don't know. It's I think it's a no not me. That was a not me. That was not me. No. No, not me
He plays a spooky play
He's like imagine being terror and attack on the Amphilicia Mountains and midnight after whistling
Well, well, I went to this I went to this Buddhist retreat and I stayed in a year, which is like basically a
Okay, it's like a tent, it's like halfway between a tent and a cabin. It's like it's kind of like it has like
you know the canvas side, but it's like a nice inside and
But but then there's like no lights out and so you had to get back before the like you got dark
And it's like and then if you're flashlight died, you're screwed
And so it's like but there were some really really cool places to hang out there. It was so cool
You can't travel in the dark side? It's easy
Well your eyes will adjust after a certain amount of time, but it's like if you're like in an unfamiliar woods
You know, you don't want to wander around in the dark like it's just like it's it's it can be but yeah
Oh, you're right. I'm familiar because I know I knew the woods. I was used to traveling in the dark and so yeah
Yeah familiar woods you're right
absolutely
I had no idea how the house of because I was just caught in there
I think then I might my flashlight battery died. I was like, oh my god, but I was able to find
But let's go. Hey tricks. Come here tricks. Do you want to say hi? You finish the you finish in the inmates?
I'll put some more here
You're like a little bird hi bird
Hi bird
This is big tricks
Okay, okay. Let's get next to Rudy
You went out you went out an hour in the
Elements go key. Oh my gosh. Yeah, so my family members don't like um fucking look a freaking low key low key
My family don't like me whistling the house and I won't whistle or so
Yeah, well camp is like camp is like not really camping like like a camp is like
You know these have cabins and it's like, you know, they have like a dining hall
Like the camp it has to be set up and like has all the resources about it
and so camps, you know, and so you're kind of like isolated in the woods once you get there, but if you're at a camp, then they can just go to the market, right?
But I like camp, I like, oh, you don't camp, oh, yeah, I thought you meant, you know, go to camp, but you camp, okay.
What do you do?
I think I don't camp, like silly rabbit.
Yeah.
To be out there be out there. So low key be out there. He you know, you know
He's a guy look easy. I always thought looking is a woman, but yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I didn't get confirmation
You prefer tense, yeah, but I like that
I like the intense are just easy to transport, but it's like a yurt is really cool
If you're gonna go glamping anybody like it's like
Little bit you prefer hammock or ten
I mean, it's like I think it's sleeping. I think hammocks are not that comfortable to sleep in we I mean hammocks are great to like
Rock around in like they in the sun, but it's not a good
But they got these new chance now they got these new hammocks now this flat so it's like some of them is not curving no more
Yeah, I mean they're always like they're improving the
aerodynamics, the products, and improving inventions, that's like it.
You know they had they always say oh there's some like some like people that say black people invented everything
They say oh black people invented absolutely everything absolutely everything was invented by a black person
And like so there's you'll see these books, but black people invented everything
I even have one I think called black people
This is guy I know that he says Jews from Greek created the whole world
Yeah, yeah, yeah
But and then also but then it's like there's also theories of like the Greeks coming from North Africa and even like
even Ethiopia like Medusa is an Ethiopian deity you know and so it's like so there are you know
there could be some of that there could be actually be Africans like a lot of Africans in
listen the world built by humans and that's it all races pitched in all around the world how about that
But it's like, I mean, I'm like, listen, I've learned a lot of interesting race theory
because I'm like, okay, I'm like, well, the races, like the different races seem like
a kind of a specialization of the certain areas where they seem to like certain people
adapted different, you know, traits to survive in the different weathers, and that's kind
of kind of a parent from like the different, you know, their, their, their, their features.
Yeah, and so I but I do have seen stuff about where there's I mean I say I've watched a lot of like people that are like really into nation of Islam and they can
Know if they're someone like the very the very black Israelis and the
All this kind of stuff and then yeah, and so they
They'll say black people invented everything and you look into it. It's like black people
So every no so every invention is like
Maybe there's a lot of inventions that we as one person just thought of it
You know, but most inventions are just adapted other inventions. And so
So there's of course like there's gonna be like no battery. I agree. He said
Ten camping is good as long as you have great memory foam embedding. You'd be alright. Yeah
Yeah, you know nice like air mattress or like a you know foam mattress and
You know because it is like a little bit a little bit rough out there and
Um, you know get some good have some good food
But I would say I would say just go glamping and like you know spend a little extra money and have like a little bit of a nicer
Experience okay, bye easy. I think easy job. I think it's almost a dive some recharge can't even set up a yeah
I know how you just put up the
The poles through the through the splits. It's a basic rocket science
So are we doing chat guys?
51 people in chat. It's pretty nice for like, you know, five or six 30 in the morning. I'm kind of impressed with myself. I never really
Well, I mean, I didn't I didn't have a feeling that
I could do, I could do, I thought I would take,
I thought I would take me longer.
I was like, oh, I was like, no one's gonna like me.
I was like, I was like, I won't appeal.
I was, it's just like, there's so many doubts
you have to go through before you, to do it.
And then it's like, when you start, you're like,
oh, I don't know what I'm doing, and it's like,
you know, but then once you get, just,
I would say, if you wanna start a YouTube channel,
go on others, go on chats, and become a modern chats,
just become kind of known in some chats, okay?
be supportive of those content creators and and and
If you know if you're gonna relationship with them, you're under mod
They're probably they'll probably let you post your your link there once in a while
Especially if you tell them you're trying to get subscribers and start streaming. I
Don't have fans that people hate watching me. That's why you don't
Understand I understand John Bayman. I understand I understand people hate me, but it's okay. It's like because that's still
Helping the algorithm even the hate helps the algorithm and it's like at the end of the day
That help the algorithm then it's like that then more people will come in and then that I'll have more people that will like me
So it's at my very slow don't go cheap on a tent get a canvas lodged in so you can have a stove inside and John
It's okay guys John you understand. I'm a gay guy
You understand like a lot of people don't like gay people like a lot of people and it's even more people than you think it's like
A lot of people are like, even if they tolerate gay people, they're like, they think it's
either wrong or disgust.
I mean, there's a couple, like, you know, so I'm used to being hated on.
And so, but it's kind of funny if people do hate me for those reasons, that reason for
the being gay, and then they still come here and watch my show.
So I don't know, sometimes people have to look at themselves, right?
Know I just agree with you. I said, yeah, I know I hate wash. Yeah, so what?
Let me see it wash 53 people in chat
And monetize channel
Active chat I think I get like 20,000 comments in chat some days over 20,000 hours a month of watch hours
So what
You're trying to say John, but I like your name by the way you related Jason Jason or Justin
I went to Jason Bay. I think Jason Bay now
He was in this movie called fake ID
Don't go cheap on it. Yeah, get a canvas town. Yeah, the canvas town is I went actually camping in Thailand, you know, we went to
I stayed in like with a family in the north, but then for a few days, we went trekking. It's called trekking
We put on a backpack and you start you just go over down these you walk all day
Go through the all these little towns villages. I said one time we saw a cow get slaughtered
Just like it was like a live cow. Yeah, and the
Beat it needs to go camping more so she can commune with her people the when to go. Oh, yeah
Wendigo is interesting. Wendigo is like basically the Wendigo is all the fears of the society into like one
Monster, you know, I mean they put it. I mean but it's like it's just like the fears of society. It's not like a real thing
And so then they can you can make peace with the Wendigo and that then it will be an ally instead of an enemy
Yeah, it's like it's kind of like the shadow. You have to kind of integrate it
Nice to go north and see some bees and palms or trees trees and not palm trees. Yeah, not like palm trees though
I'm just like, you know, it's like very California. We have a lot of palm trees around here
Love schools running up them
They're pretty I like palm trees, but yeah, I like other trees too. We have a lot for work from pals birdies
We have a lot of pepper trees
Sure pretty cool. I had one actually in front of my house
At my Glendale house, my grandfather used to grow rose bushes and so at my Glendale house
They came over and they transplanted the rose bushes up in front of there
You'd love to see me on here sometime, but you understand you don't want oh, yeah
Yeah, come on come up sometime go key. I know you're a mod and a member, you know if you're be like
Come on panel. I'm sure the chat the panel of the chat would like to talk to you
You know chat chat really doesn't come here for me. I don't think they're coming in for the other interesting people and
I'm just I'm just tolerated on my own show, but you know a lot of people are watching. Okay, I
I'm just I'm just kidding. I don't I do not take offense
So I got that left. Okay, you have been more I've been actually back home. I'm just have a little tobacco
Yeah
So what we've got Sam for today, you know, I got
I'm not gonna drink the last I'm gonna save the other drink for the night
That might get some the cars a little bit
58 people awesome guys
You like you you like it it's where it's still time. Thank you, Randy. I
Try to like have a good
I mean, even if like, people don't like the guest,
it's like, I really don't like me.
I hope they like the guest, but if they don't like the guest,
I hope they like me.
And like, one of us, somebody's gonna be appealing
to have people like the show.
It's like, you know, it's like,
you have to like, like at least one person, right?
Do you need a tick check?
Has anyone done a tick check on you on my,
or a low key?
Low key into the text for ticks?
I'm sure.
Yeah
I'd like to have like a big variety of
Thing and that's what's good. That's why I was like, okay if I have I could do tarot and so that's gonna be something
That maybe like not a lot of people know about but some people will and it's like our night
I can introduce people to it and it's like it's something that's interesting and something that can
Be conversational even if I don't know the person I can talk to them
And also something I can like you know do